<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="script.module.inputstreamhelper" name="InputStream Helper" version="0.5.10" provider-name="emilsvennesson, dagwieers, mediaminister, horstle">
  <requires>
    <!--py3 compliant-->
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pysocks" version="1.6.8" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <!-- This is needed to get an add-on icon -->
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="de_DE">Kodi InputStream und DRM Wiedergabe einfach gemacht</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Βοηθός Inputstream για το Kodi και εύκολη αναπαραγωγή DRM</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi InputStream and DRM playback made easy</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Kodi InputStream y reproducción DRM echa fácil</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">La lecture Kodi InputStream et DRM en toute simplicité</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Kodi InputStream olakšava reprodukciju DRM zaštićenog sadržaja</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieses einfache Kodi-Modul macht das Leben für Addon Entwickler einfacher, die auf InputStream basierte Addons und DRM Wiedergabe angewiesen sind.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Μία απλή μονάδα για το Kodi η οποία διευκολύνει την ζωή των προγραμματιστών οι οποίοι εξαρτώνται από τα πρόσθετσ InputStream και αναπαραγωγή τύπου DRM.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">A simple Kodi module that makes life easier for add-on developers relying on InputStream based add-ons and DRM playback.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Un módulo Kodi simple que hace la vida más fácil para los desarrolladores de complementos que dependen de complementos basados en InputStream y reproducción de DRM.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Un simple module Kodi qui simplifie la vie des développeurs de modules complémentaires en s’appuyant sur des modules complémentaires basés sur InputStream et sur la lecture de DRM.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Jednostavan Kodi modul koji olakšava razvijanje dodataka koji se temelje na InputStream dodatku i reprodukciji DRM zaštićenog sadržaja.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Простой модуль для Kodi, который облегчает жизнь разработчикам дополнений, с использованием InputStream дополнений и воспроизведения DRM контента.</description>
    <news>
v0.5.10 (2022-04-18)
- Fix automatic submission of release
- Update German translation
- Fix update_frequency setting
- Fix install_from
- Improve/Fix Widevine extraction from Chrome OS images

v0.5.9 (2022-03-22)
- Update Croatian translation
- Replace deprecated LooseVersion
- Fix http_get decode error
- Option to install Widevine from specified source
    </news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper/wiki</website>
    <source>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.metadatautils"
       name="Metadata and Artwork module"
       version="1.0.19"
       provider-name="marcelveldt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8" />
        <import addon="script.module.thetvdb" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.musicbrainz" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Metadata and artwork from common sources like TMDB, IMDB, TADB and fanart.tv </summary>
        <description lang="en">
            The metadata and artwork module for Kodi provides rich metadata, including artwork for
            various metatypes by scraping (and caching) this information from sites like TMDB, musicbrainz and fanart.tv.[CR][CR]
            This product uses the TMDb API but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb
        </description>
		<summary lang="es">Metadatos e ilustraciones de fuentes comunes como TMDB, IMDB, TADB y fanart.tv </summary>
        <description lang="es">
            El módulo de metadatos e ilustraciones para Kodi proporciona metadatos enriquecidos, incluidas ilustraciones para
            varios metatipos al raspar (y almacenar en caché) esta información de sitios como TMDB, musicbrainz y fanart.tv. [CR] [CR]
            Este producto utiliza la API TMDb pero no está avalado ni certificado por TMDb
        </description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.metadatautils</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.arrow"
       name="arrow"
       version="0.15.5"
       provider-name="crsmithdev, Razzeee">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache" version="1.5.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Arrow: better dates and times for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en">Packed for Kodi from https://github.com/crsmithdev/arrow</description>
	<summary lang="es">Arrow: mejores fechas y horarios para Python</summary>
    <description lang="es">Empaquetado para Kodi de https://github.com/crsmithdev/arrow</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Apache2</license>
    <source>https://github.com/Razzeee/script.module.arrow</source>
    <email>beenje AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.weathericons.default"
       name="Weather Icons - Default"
       version="1.1.8"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.resource.images"
             type="weather" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Default Weather Icons</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Iconos del tiempo por defecto</summary>
    <description lang="en">Default set of Weather Icons shipped with Kodi</description>
    <description lang="es">Conjunto predeterminado de iconos del tiempo para Kodi</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.estuary" version="2.0.27" name="Estuary" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodi's standard brugerflade).</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65 und Piers. (Kodi Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary, creado por phil65 and Piers (skin por defecto de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Estuary skin por phil65 y Piers. (El skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autorilt phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary on phil65:n luoma Kodin oletusulkoasu.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d'origine de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary da phil65 e Piers. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi's standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary (стандартная обложка Kodi). Авторы: phil65 and Piers.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi's standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodnŏ skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d'entendre i d'utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Intenta ser fácil para los usuarios de Kodi de primera vez para entender y usar.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary on oletusulkoasu Kodin versiosta 17.0 lähtien. Se pyrkii olemaan helppo ymmärtää ja käyttää Kodin ensikäyttäjille. </description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l'habillage d'origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban.  Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e usare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0.&amp;#10;Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Pokúša sa byť pre prvotných používateľov Kodi jednoduchým na pochopenie a používanie.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s'elimina pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Estuary yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Desinstalarlo puede causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary es el skin por defecto para Kodi, su eliminación puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Estuary Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary on Kodin oletusulkoasu, sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary est l'habillage d'origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Estuary er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">EstuaryはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon	id="script.module.defusedxml"
		name="defusedxml"
		version="0.6.0"
		provider-name="Christian Heimes">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.python.module"
		library="lib" />
	<extension
		point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">defusedxml -- defusing XML bombs and other exploits</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://github.com/tiran/defusedxml</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">defusedxml -- defusing XML bombas y otras hazañas</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Empaquetado para KODI desde https://github.com/tiran/defusedxml</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>PSF</license>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/defusedxml/</website>
		<source>https://github.com/tiran/defusedxml</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.xbmcswift2" name="xbmcswift2" provider-name="Jonathan Beluch (jbel), enen92" version="13.0.0">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <source>https://github.com/XBMC-Addons/script.module.xbmcswift2</source>
    <license>GPL-3.0</license>
    <summary lang="en">xbmcswift2 is a small framework to ease development of KODI addons.</summary>
    <description lang="en">xbmcswift2 is a small framework to ease development of KODI addons.</description>
	 <summary lang="es">xbmcswift2 es un pequeño marco para facilitar el desarrollo de complementos KODI.</summary>
    <description lang="es">xbmcswift2 es un pequeño marco para facilitar el desarrollo de complementos KODI.</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.Virtual.Gym"
       name="Gym Virtual"
       version="1.0.2"
       provider-name="Netai">
<requires>
	<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	<import addon="script.module.urlresolver" version="5.0.00"/>
	<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.00"/>
</requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>

  <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://github.com/tvaddonsco/tva-resolvers-repo/raw/master/zips/</datadir>
  </dir>
  <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
</dir>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="es">Gym Virtual </summary>
    <language>es</language>
    <description lang="es">Ponte en forma en tu propia casa!</description>
     <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyautogui"
	name="PyAutoGUI"
	version="0.9.51"
	provider-name="Al Sweigart">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">PyAutoGUI is a cross-platform GUI automation Python module for human beings. Used to programmatically control the mouse and keyboard.</summary>
		<forum></forum>
		<website>https://pyautogui.readthedocs.io/</website>
		<license>see LICENSE.txt</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<source>https://github.com/asweigart/pyautogui</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="pvr.hts" version="4.4.21.1" name="Tvheadend HTSP Client" provider-name="Adam Sutton, Sam Stenvall, Lars Op den Kamp, Kai Sommerfeld">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.pvr" version="5.10.3"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.pvrclient" library_linux="pvr.hts.so.4.4.21"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Kodi se voorprogram vir Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Клиент за „Tvheadend“</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Frontal de Kodi per a Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Rozhraní Kodi pro Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Blaen Kodi ar gyfer Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Kodis brugerflade til Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Kodi-PVR-Client für Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Το frontend του Kodi για το Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Interfaz Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Interfaz Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">El frontend de Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Kodi liides Tvheadend'ile</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Kodin Tvheadend-asiakasohjelma</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Frontale Kodi pour Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Interface logicielle pour Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Interface do Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">לקוח טלוויזיה חיה עבור Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Kodi sučelje za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Kodi előtét a TVHeadend-hez</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Frontend Kodi untuk Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Kodi framendi fyrir Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Frontend di Kodi per Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">TVheadend 用 Kodi フロントエンド</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Tvheadend 을 위한 Kodi 프론트엔드</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Kodi naudotojo sąsaja skirta Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Kodi galasistēma Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="mn_MN">Tvheadend зориулагдсан Kodi-ийн нүүр</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Bahagian hadapan Kodi untuk </summary>
    <summary lang="mt_MT">Faċċata ta' Kodi għat- TVheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Kodis grenseflate for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Kodi's frontend voor Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Klient telewizji dla Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Frontend Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Interface Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Interfața Kodi pentru Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Интерфейс Kodi для Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Kodi rozhranie pre Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Kodijev vmesnik za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sq_AL">Frontend i Kodi'së për Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Kodi-јев интерфејс за Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Kodijev interfejs za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Kodi's frontend för Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="szl">Frontend do Tvheadend ôd Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="te_IN">Tvheadend కోసం కోడి యొక్క ఫ్రంటెండ్</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси Kodi барои Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Tvheadend için Kodi ön ucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Інтерфейс Kodi для Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Giao tiếp Kodi cho Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Kodi 的 Tvheadend 前端</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Kodi的Tvheadend前端介面</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Tvheadend voorprogram; ondersteun stroom van Lewendige TV &amp; Opnames, EPG, Tydhouers</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Клиент за „Tvheadend“. Поддържа телевизия на живо, записване, електронен програмен справочник и броячи.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Frontal de Tvheadend; compatible amb la transmissió de TV en directe i enregistraments, guia electrònica de programació (EPG), temporitzadors</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Rozhraní Tvheadend; podporuje streamování živého vysílání a nahrávání, televizní program, časovače.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Blaen Tvheadend: cefnogi ffrydio Teledu Byw a Recordio, Amserlenni, Amseryddion</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Tvheadend-brugerflade; understøtter streaming af direkte tv og optagelser, EPG og timere</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">PVR-Client für Tvheadend. Unterstützt TV &amp; Aufnahmen, Programm-Guide (EPG) und Timer.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Frontend για το Tvheadend. Υποστηρίζει ροές Live TV &amp; Εγγραφές, EPG, Χρονοδιακόπτες</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Interfaz Tvheadend; soporta la reproducción de TV en vivo, grabación, guía de programación, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Interfaz Tvheadend; soporta la reproducción de TV en vivo, grabación, guía de programación, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Frontend de Tvheadend; Compatible con la transmisión de TV en directo y Grabaciones, EPG, Temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Tvheadend'i liides. Toetab telekanalite striimimist ja salvestamist ning elektroonilist saatekava.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tvheadend-asiakasohjelma. Tukee suorien tv-lähetysten ja tallennusten katsomista, ohjelmaopasta ja ohjelmien ajastamista.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Frontale pour Tvheadend, prenant en charge la diffusion en continu des télés en direct et les enregistrements, le GÉP et les minuteries</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Interface logicielle pour Tvheadend gérant la lecture en continu de la TV en direct et des enregistrements, le guide électronique des programmes TV et les programmations.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Interface Tvheadend; soporta a transmisión de TV en directo e Gravacións, Guía, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">לקוח טלוויזיה חיה של Tvheadend. תומך בהזרמת שידורים חיים והקלטות, האזנה לרדיו, הצגת לוח שידורים ותזמון הקלטות.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Tvheadend pozadinski softver podržava gledanje i snimanje TV programa, elektronski programski vodič (EPG) i zakazano snimanje.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">TVHeadend előtét. Élő adások és felvételek támogatása EPG-vel és időzítéssel</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Frontend Tvheadend; mendukung menangkap siaran TV Live &amp; Rekaman, EPG, Timer</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Tvheadend framendi; styður streymingu á beinum útsendingum og upptökum, rafrænum sjónvarpsvísum (EGP), tímatökur</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Frontend di Tvheadend; supporta lo streaming di Live TV &amp; Registrazione, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">TVheadend フロントエンドです。ライブTVストリーミング、録画、EPG、タイマーをサポートしています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Tvheadend 프론트엔드; TV 시청 &amp; 녹화, EPG, 타이머 지원</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Tvheadend naudotojo sąsaja; palaiko televizijos transliacijas ir įrašus, EPG, laikmačius</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Tvheadend galasistēma; atbalsta tieštaides TV un ierakstu straumēšanu, EPG, taimerus</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="mn_MN">Tvheadend нүүр; Live TV &amp; бичлэг дамжуулалт, EPG, Timer</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Bahagian hadapan Tvheadend; menyokong penstriman  Langsung &amp; Rakaman, EPG, Pemasa TV</description>
    <description lang="mt_MT">Faċċata ta' TVheadend; jiflaħ għal streaming ta' TV Lajv u rekordings, EPG, Arloġġi</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Tvheadend-grenseflate; støtte for visning av direkte-TV og opptak, EPG, tidsur</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Tvheadend frontend. Ondersteuning van streaming, Live-TV &amp; opnames, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Klient telewizji dla Tvheadend obsługuje transmisję kanałów radiowych i telewizyjnych, nagrywanie i harmonogram nagrań oraz funkcje przewodnika telewizyjnego.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Tvheadend; suporta streaming de TV Ao Vivo e Gravada, EPG, Agendamentos</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Interface Tvheadend. Suporta transmissão e gravação de TV em direto, EPG e temporizadores.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Partea din față pentru Tvheadend; suportă difuzarea în flux a televiziunii în direct și a înregistrăriilor, EPG, Cronometre</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Интерфейс для Tvheadend. Поддерживает просмотр и запись ТВ, EPG и таймеры</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Rozhranie pre Tvheadend; je podporované streamovanie živého televízneho vysielania a nahrávok, EPG, časovačov</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Vmesnik za Tvheadend; podpira pretakanje televizije v živo &amp; posnetkov, EPG, časovnike</description>
    <description lang="sq_AL">Tvheadend frotnend përkrahën transmetimin e Live TV'së, EPG'së dhe "timer'ë"</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Tvheadend интерфејс; подржава стримовање ТВ Уживо &amp; Снимака, EPG, Тајмере</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS@latin">Tvheadend interfejs; podržava strimovanje TV Uživo &amp; Snimaka, EPG, Tajmere</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Tvheadend frontend; stödjer strömning av Live-TV &amp; inspelningar, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="szl">Frontend Tvheadend; podpiyrŏ strumiyniowaniy TV, nagrań, EPG i minutnikōw</description>
    <description lang="te_IN">Tvheadend ఫ్రంటెండ్; Live TV &amp; రికార్డింగ్స్, EPG, టైమర్లు , స్ట్రీమింగ్ మద్దతు కలదు</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси Tvheadend; дастгирии ҷараёни Сабтҳо, Вақтсанҷҳо, Live TV ва EPG</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Tvheadend ön ucu; Canlı TV akışı ve kayıt yapabilme, EPG ve zamanlayıcıları destekler</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Інтерфейс для Tvheadend; підтримує передачу і запис потокового телебачення, EPG (телегід) і таймери.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Giao tiếp cho Tvheadend; hỗ trợ truyền phát và thu chương trình Live TV, hẹn giờ, và hiển thị lịch chiếu (EPG)</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">Tvheadend 前端，支持直播电视和录像流媒体、电子节目单、定时器</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Tvheadend前端，支援的串流媒體包含有直播電視和錄製節目，電子節目表，定時器 等</description>
    <platform/>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.coreelec"
		name="CoreELEC Add-ons"
		version="9.2"
		provider-name="CoreELEC">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository"
		name="CoreELEC Add-ons">
		<info>https://addons.coreelec.org/9.2/Amlogic/arm/addons.xml.gz</info>
		<checksum verify="sha256">https://addons.coreelec.org/9.2/Amlogic/arm/addons.xml.gz?sha256</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://addons.coreelec.org/9.2/Amlogic/arm</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>CoreELEC Add-ons</summary>
		<description>The CoreELEC add-on repository contains Kodi PVR Clients and Servers, Screensavers, Visualisations, and more. Add-ons in this repository are maintained and supported by CoreELEC staff and YOU the community. If you find a broken or non-working add-on please report it via the forums, or help by submitting fixes via GitHub.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.elementum" name="Elementum" version="0.1.97" provider-name="elgatito">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="navigation.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/site-packages" />
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="navigation.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="ru">Elementum: Стриминг видео</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Elementum: Media streaming</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Elementum: Medijsko strujanje</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Elementum: Transmisión de medios</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Elementum: medieströmning</summary>
        <description lang="ru">Elementum это дополнение для поиска и воспроизведения торрентов. Дополнение не ходит на запрещенные сайты самостоятельно. Хотя, для поиска используются дополнения (называемые провайдерами), которые устанавливаются отдельно.[CR]Этот проект является ответвлением хорошо извесных, но не поддерживаемых Pulsar/Quasar от steeve и scakemyer.</description>
        <description lang="en">Elementum is a torrent finding and streaming engine. It doesn't go on torrent websites for legal reasons. However, it calls specially crafted add-ons (called providers) that are installed separately.[CR]This project is a fork of the well known, but no longer maintained Pulsar/Quasar projects from steeve and scakemyer.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Elementum je pogon pretraživanja i strujanja. Ne posjećuje torrent web stranice iz pravnih razloga. Ipak, koristi posebno napravljene dodatke (nazvane pružatelji usluge) koji su instalirani odvojeno.[CR]Ovaj projekt je ogranak dobro poznatih, ali više ne održavanih Pulsar/Quasar projekata od autora steevea i scakemyera.</description>
        <description lang="es">Elementum es un motor de búsqueda y transmisión torrent. No navega por sitios web torrent por razones legales. Sin embargo, llama a complementos especialmente diseñados para ello (denominados providers o proveedores) que se instalan por separado.[CR]Este proyecto es un fork de los bien conocidos, pero ya sin soporte proyectos Pulsar/Quasar de steeve y scakemyer.[CR]</description>
        <description lang="sv">Elementum är en torrentsöknings- och strömningsmotor. Det går inte till torrentwebbplatser av juridiska skäl. Den anropar dock speciellt utformade tillägg (kallade leverantörer) som installeras separat.[CR]Detta projekt är en förgrening av de välkända, men inte längre underhållna Pulsar/Quasar-projekten av steeve och scakemyer. </description>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Автор дополнения не несёт ответственности за скачивание или поиск информации и содержимого в этом дополнении. Автор никак не связан с Kodi, командой Kodi, или XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not own or host any content found within this Addon. The author is not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Autor ovog dodatka ne posjeduje i ne distribuira bilo kakav sadržaj koji je pronađen. Autor nije povezan sa ili na bilo koji drugi način bilo sa Kodijem, Team Kodijem ili XBMC fundacijom.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">El autor no posee ni aloja ningún contenido que se encuentre a través de este complemento. El autor no está unido ni relacionado de ninguna manera con Kodi, Team Kodi, o XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Skaparen äger inte eller är värd av något innehåll som finns i detta tillägg. Författaren är inte ansluten till eller på något annat sätt en del av Kodi, Team Kodi eller XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
        <language>en el es de fi fr he hr it nl pt ro sk sv</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>http://elementum.surge.sh/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/elgatito/plugin.video.elementum</source>
        <forum></forum>
        <license>Non commercial. See https://github.com/elgatito/plugin.video.elementum/blob/master/LICENSE</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/home.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/movies.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/webui.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.tubecast" name="TubeCast" version="1.4.5" provider-name="enen92">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.bottle" version="0.12.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="5.5.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Cast videos from the Youtube application to Kodi</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_PT">Cast de vídeos a partir da aplicação móvel Youtube para o Kodi</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Transmitir videos desde la aplicación de Youtube a Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">An implementation of the Cast V1 protocol in Kodi to act as a player for the Youtube mobile application</description>
        <description lang="pt_PT">Uma implementação do protocolo Cast V1 no Kodi para este funcionar como player externo remotamente controlado pela aplicação móvel do YouTube</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Una implementación del protocolo Cast V1 en Kodi para actuar como reproductor externo para la aplicación móvil de Youtube</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=329153</forum>
        <email>enen92@kodi.tv</email>
        <source>https://github.com/enen92/script.tubecast</source>
        <news>
            [fix] missing ctt key (tks romainreignier)
            [fix] add default id if friendlyname is missing
        </news>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This is not a full chromecast implementation nor will it ever be. It will only work as long as Google keep backwards compatibility with the cast v1 protocol in the Youtube application. Deeply inspired by Leapcast and gotubecast projects</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_PT">Este addon não é uma implementação completa do protocolo cast nem nunca será. Apenas funcionará enquanto a Google mantiver a retrocompatibilidade com o protocolo cast v1 na aplicação móvel do youtube. Inspirado no Leapcast e gotubecast</disclaimer>
	    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Esta no es una implementación completa de Chromecast ni lo será nunca. Solo funcionará mientras Google mantenga la compatibilidad con el protocolo Cast v1 en la aplicación Youtube. Profundamente inspirado por los proyectos Leapcast y gotubecast</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/img/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/img/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/img/screenshot-0.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/img/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/img/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/img/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simpleplugin3"
   name="SimplePlugin 3"
   version="3.0.6"
   provider-name="Roman V.M.; vl.maksime">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.16.0.4"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="libs" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">SimplePlugin micro-framework</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">SimplePlugin micro-framework that simplifies Kodi content plugin programming.</description>
    <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>http://vlmaksime.github.io/script.module.simpleplugin/</website>
    <email>vl.maksime@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/vlmaksime/script.module.simpleplugin</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.netflix" name="Netflix" version="1.12.9" provider-name="libdev + jojo + asciidisco + caphm + castagnait">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.signals" version="0.0.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.17.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="packages/mysql-connector-python"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Plugin pro sledování filmů, seriálů online z Netflixu</description>
    <disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Použití tohoto doplňku nemusí být ve vaší zemi pobytu legální - před instalací dbejte na vaše zákony.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Addon für Netflix VOD-Dienste</description>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Möglicherweise ist die Verwendung dieses Addons in Ihrem Land illegal, Sie sollten dies unbedingt vor der Installation überprüfen.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Netflix VOD Services Add-on</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">The use of this add-on may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Νέτφλιξ</summary>
    <description lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο υπηρεσιών κατά παραγγελία του Νέτφλιξ</description>
    <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Η χρήση αυτού του προσθέτου μπορεί να μην είναι νόμιμη στην χώρα που κατοικείτε - παρακαλώ ελέγξτε τους τοπικούς νόμους πριν την εγκατάσταση.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Bekijk Netflix films en tvprogramma's in Kodi.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Sommige delen van deze add-on zijn mogelijk onwettig in jouw land - raadpleeg de lokale wetgeving alvorens deze add-on te installeren.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Netflix VOD サービスアドオン</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ja_JP">一部の国では、このアドオンを使用するのが不法でありますので、設置する前に必ず関連法律を確認してください</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Netflix VOD 서비스애드온</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ko_KR">일부 국가에서는 이 애드온을 사용하는 것이 불법일 수도 있으니, 설치하기전 관련 법을 확인하기 바랍니다.</disclaimer>
    <description lang="it_IT">Netflix Add-on servizi VOD</description>
    <disclaimer lang="it_IT">L'utilizzo di questo add-on potrebbe non essere legale nel vostro paese di residenza - si prega di verificare le leggi in vigore prima dell'installazione.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Complemento para los Servicios VOD de Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">El uso de este complemento puede no ser legal en su país de residencia - Por favor, consulte las leyes locales antes de instalarlo.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Netflix VOD kiegészítő a Kodihoz</description>
    <disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Előfordulhat, hogy a kiegészítő használata nem törvényes az Ön országában - telepítés előtt tájékozódjon a helyi törvényekről</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Add-on para os serviços VOD do Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">O uso deste addon pode não ser legal no seu país de residência - por favor, verifique as suas leis locais antes de instalar.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Netflix VOD Hizmetleri Eklentisi</description>
    <disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Bu eklentinin bazı bölümleri ikamet ettiğiniz ülkede yasal olmayabilir - lütfen yüklemeden önce yerel yasalarınıza bakın.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Add-on pentru servicii video la cerere Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Utilizarea acestui add-on ar putea fi ilegală în țara în care locuiți - vă rugăm să verificați legile locale înainte de instalare.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Netflix VOD Service-tillägg</description>
    <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Användandet av detta tillägg kanske inte är lagligt i ditt hemland - kontrollera med dina lokala lagar innan du installerar.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="zh_CN">Netflix VOD服务附加组件</description>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">此附加组件在您的居住国可能不合法-请在安装前与您当地的法律核对。</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Extension Netflix SVoD</description>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">L'utilisation de cette extension n'est peut-être pas légale dans votre pays de résidence - renseignez-vous avant de l'installer</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka dla usług VOD serwisu Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Korzystanie z tego dodatku może być niezgodne z prawem w twoim kraju zamieszkania - przed zainstalowaniem zapoznaj się z lokalnymi przepisami.</disclaimer>
    <summary lang="he_IL">Netflix</summary>
    <description lang="he_IL">תוסף VOD לשירות של Netflix</description>
    <disclaimer lang="he_IL">השימוש בתוסף זה עלול להיות לא חוקי במדינת מגוריך - אנא בדוק את החוק ברשות המקומית לפני ההתקנה</disclaimer>
	<assets>
      <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <language>en cs de es fr he hr hu it ja ko nl pl pt ro sv tr zh</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://www.netflix.com</website>
    <email></email>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=329767</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/CastagnaIT/plugin.video.netflix</source>
    <news>
v1.12.9 (2022-02-05)
- Switched to MSL manifest v2 as default (Dev.note without sid/challenge)
- Add "MSL manifest version" expert setting to allow switch to MSL manifest v1
- Fix error "This title is not available to watch instantly" when using MSL manifest v1
    </news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.idna" name="idna" version="2.10.0" provider-name="Kim Davies">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Internationalized Domain Names for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Internationalized Domain Names for Python</description>
    <license>BSD-3-Clause</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>https://github.com/kjd/idna</website>
    <source>https://github.com/kjd/idna</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.system.docker"
       name="Docker"
       version="9.2.127"
       provider-name="Team CoreELEC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>

  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Docker is an open-source engine that automates the deployment of any application as a lightweight, portable, self-sufficient container that will run virtually anywhere.</summary>
    <description>
Docker containers can encapsulate any payload, and will run consistently on and between virtually any server. The same container that a developer builds and tests on a laptop will run at scale, in production*, on VMs, bare-metal servers, OpenStack clusters, public instances, or combinations of the above.
    </description>
    <disclaimer>

    </disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
127
- Rebuild tini without -DMINIMAL=ON to fix 'docker run --init'

126
- Update to docker 18.09.7

125
- Update to docker 18.09.5

124
- Update to docker 18.09.4

123
- Update to docker 18.09.3

122
- Update to docker 18.09.1

121
- Update to docker 18.09.1-rc1

120
- Update to docker 18.09.1-beta1

119
- Update to docker 18.09.0

118
- Update to docker 18.06.1-ce

117
- Update to docker 17.10

116
- change to new project structure

114
- Enable journald buildtag

113
- Update to docker 1.13.1
- Update to golang 1.7.5

112
- Update to docker 1.13.0
- Use journald log driver
- Add docker-init (tini)

111
- Add temporary cleanup for old systemd service

110
- Update to docker 1.12.5
- Adjust the systemd service file

109
- Update to docker 1.12.3
- Include ctop utility

108
- Update to docker 1.12.2

107
- Update to docker 1.12.1

106
- Include missing docker-proxy

105
- Update to docker 1.12.0
- Update to golang 1.6.3
- Use overlay2 driver (new installs only)
- Remove docker-containerd-ctr

104
- Update to docker 1.11.2

103
- Allow using kodi notifications based on Docker events API

102
- Update to docker 1.11.1

101
- Update to golang 1.6.2
- Update to docker 1.11.0

100
- Update for LibreELEC 8.0

100
- Initial release
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>

    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="webinterface.default"
  version="18.x-2.4.6"
  name="Kodi web interface - Chorus2"
  provider-name="jez500, Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Default web interface</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Interfaz web predeterminada </summary>
    <description lang="en">Browse and interact with your Music, Movies, TV Shows and more via a web browser. Stream music and videos to your browser. Edit and manage your masQelec media library.</description>
    <description lang="es">Navega e interactúa con tu música, películas, programas de TV y más a través de un navegador web. Transmita música y videos a su navegador. Edite y administre su biblioteca multimedia masQelec.</description>
	<platform>all</platform>
    <language>es</language>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/chorus2</source>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=183451</forum>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>images/turntable.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>screenshots/now-playing.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/search.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/artists.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/artist.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/tv.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/movie.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/settings.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/addons.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>screenshots/edit-media.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="2.1.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="script" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="subtitles" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="lyrics" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="weather" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="library" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="screensaver" schema="script.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="plugin" schema="pluginsource.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="context.item" schema="contextitem.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.kodi-six"
       name="Kodi Six"
       version="0.1.3"
       provider-name="Roman V.M.">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="libs" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Wrappers around Kodi Python API for seamless Python 2/3 compatibility</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Wrappers around Kodi Python API that normalize handling of textual and byte strings in Python 2 and 3.</description>
	<summary lang="es_ES">Contenedores alrededor de la API de Kodi Python para una compatibilidad perfecta con Python 2/3</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Contenedores alrededor de la API de Kodi Python que normalizan el manejo de cadenas de texto y bytes en Python 2 y 3.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v.3</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=327883</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/romanvm/kodi.six</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
    <news>0.1.3:
- Fix non-UTF-8 byte string decoding in Python 2.</news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.certifi" name="certifi" version="2021.10.8" provider-name="Certifi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python package for providing Mozilla's CA Bundle.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Certifi is a carefully curated collection of Root Certificates for validating the trustworthiness of SSL certificates while verifying the identity of TLS hosts. It has been extracted from the Requests project.</description>
    <license>MPL-2.0</license>
    <website>https://github.com/certifi/python-certifi</website>
    <source>https://github.com/certifi/python-certifi</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.subtitles.opensubtitles"
       name="OpenSubtitles.org"
       version="5.2.14"
       provider-name="amet, opensubtitles">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module"
             library="service.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>OpenSubtitles</summary>
    <description lang="en">Anonymously search and download subtitles for movies and TV-Series from OpenSubtitles.org without log-in. Search in 75 languages, 4.000.000+ subtitles, daily updates. </description>
	<description lang="at">Pelis and Subtítulos TV en munches llingües, milenta de subtítulos traducíos y xubíos caldía. Descarga llibre dende la fonte, sofitu API, millones d'usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="br">Istitloù Filmoù ha TV e meur a yezh, miliadoù a istitloù troet hag uskarget bemdez. Pellgargadenn digoust diouzh ar vammenn, skoazell an API, millionoù a implijerien.</description>
	<description lang="ca">Subtítols de films i televisió en múltiples idiomes, milers de subtítols traduïts carregats diàriament. Descàrrega gratuïta des de la font, suport de l'API, amb milions d'usuaris.</description>
	<description lang="cs">Titulky k filmům a seriálům v mnoha jazycích, denně tisíce nahraných přeložených titulků. Stažení zadarmo přímo od zdroje, podpora API, milióny uživatelů.</description>
	<description lang="de">Film- und TV-Untertitel in vielen Sprachen, täglicher Upload von tausenden übersetzten Untertiteln. Freier Download von der Quelle, API-Unterstützung, Millionen Nutzer</description>
	<description lang="el">Ταινίες και Σειρές σε όλες τις γλώσσες, χιλιάδες μεταφρασμένοι υπότιτλοι ανεβαίνουν καθημερινά, κατεβάστε δωρεάν , υποστήριξη API από εκατομμύρια χρήστες</description>
	<description lang="eo">Filmaj kaj Televidaj subtekstoj en multaj lingvoj, miloj da tradukitaj subtekstoj ĉiutage alŝutataj. Senpaga elŝuto de fonto, API-subteno, miloj da uzantoj.</description>
	<description lang="es">Películas y Subtítulos en diversos idiomas, miles de subtítulos traducidos subidos diariamente. Descarge gratis, soporte API, millones de usuarios.</description>
	<description lang="et">Sadu Filmi ja TV Serjaalide subtiitrid erinevates keeltes laetakse üles igapäev. tasuta allalaadimine ja abi, rohkem kui miljon kasutajat.</description>
	<description lang="eu">Film eta Telebista azpitituluak hizkuntza anitzetan, milaka azpititulu itzuliak igotzen dira egunero. Doan jaitsi iturburutik, API sostengua, milioika erabiltzaile.</description>
	<description lang="fi">Tekstityksiä useilla kielillä elokuviin ja TV-Sarjoihin, tuhansia uusia tekstityksiä päivittäin, ilmainen lataus, API tuki, miljoonia käyttäjiä.</description>
	<description lang="fr">Les sous-titres de film et téléfilm en plusieurs langues, des milliers de sous-titres traduits tous les jours. Bénéficiez de téléchargements gratuits depuis la source, du support API, une d'une communauté de millions d'utilisateurs.</description>
	<description lang="hi">मूवी और टीवी उपशीर्षक कई भाषाओं में अनुवाद उपशीर्षक के हजारों दैनिक अपलोड की गई। मुफ्त डाउनलोड स्रोत से , एपीआई समर्थन, उपयोगकर्ताओं के लाखों लोगों की ।</description>
	<description lang="hr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, tisuće prijevoda postavljenih svaki dan. Besplatno preuzimanje s izvora, podrška za API, milijuni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="hu">Film és TV feliratok több nyelven, naponta több ezer lefordított felirat feltöltés. Ingyenes letöltés a forrástól, API támogatás, több millió felhasználó.</description>
	<description lang="id">Subjudul film dan serial TV dalam multibahasa, ribuan subjudul diterjemah dan diunggah setiap harinya. Pengunduhan gratis dari sumber, didukung fitur antarmuka pemrograman aplikasi, dan jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="is">Textar fyrir myndir og sjónvarpsþ. á mörgum tungumálum, þúsundir af þýddum textum upphlaðið daglega. Frítt niðurhal frá síðu, API stuðningur, milljónir notenda.</description>
	<description lang="it">Sottotitoli di Film e TV in più lingue,migliaia di sottotitoli tradotti caricati ogni giorno.Download gratuito,supporto API, milioni di utenti.</description>
	<description lang="ja">映画やテレビの字幕をさまざまな言語で。毎日数多くの翻訳字幕がアップロードされています。ソースを無料ダウンロード、API 対応、数百万を超えるユーザー。</description>
	<description lang="ka">სუბტიტრები ფილმებისა და ტვ-სთვის მრავალ ენაზე. ათასობიტ თარგმნილი სუბტიტრის ატვირთვა ყოველდღიურად. უდასო ჩამოტვირტვა წყაროდან, API მხარდაჭერა, მილიონობით მომხმარებელი</description>
	<description lang="km">អត្ថបទរឿងសម្រាប់ ខ្សែភាពយន្ត និងកម្មវិធីទូរទស្សន៍​ ជាភាសាជាច្រើន រួមនឹងអត្ថបទរឿងបកប្រែរាប់ពាន់​រឿង​ដែល​ត្រូវបាន​អ័ពឡូដជារៀងរាល់ថ្ងៃ។ ទាញយកដោយឥតគិតថ្លៃពីប្រភពដើម គាំទ្រ API និងមានអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់រាប់លាននាក់។ </description>
	<description lang="ko">Movie and TV Subtitles in multiple languages, thousands of translated subtitles uploaded daily. Free download from source, API support, millions of users.</description>
	<description lang="ms">Sarikata TV dan Movie dalam pelbagai bahasa, ribuan terjemahan sarikata dimuat-naik setiap hari.Muat-turun percuma dari sumber utama, sokongan API, jutaan pengguna.</description>
	<description lang="nl">Ondertitels voor films en tv-series in meerdere talen, dagelijks upload van duizenden vertaalde ondertitels. Gratis downloaden van de bron, API ondersteuning, miljoenen gebruikers.</description>
	<description lang="no">Undertekster for film og TV på mange språk, med tusener av nye oversettelser hver dag. Vi har gratis nedlasting av undertekster, API-support, og mange millioner brukere.</description>
	<description lang="pt-br">Milhares de legendas para filmes e seriados de TV, em vários idiomas, são traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis, suporte API e milhões de usuários.</description>
	<description lang="pl">Napisy do filmów i seriali w wielu językach. Tysiące napisów dodawanych codziennie. Darmowe pobranie, miliony użytkowników.</description>
	<description lang="pt">Legendas de filmes e séries de TV em vários idiomas, milhares de legendas traduzidas e enviadas diariamente. Download grátis a partir da fonte, suporte API, milhões de utilizadores.</description>
	<description lang="ro">Subtitrari pentru filme in multe limbi, mii de subtitrari traduse si încărcate in fiecare zi. Descărca gratuit de la sursă, suport API, milioane de utilizatori.</description>
	<description lang="ru">Кино и ТВ субтитры на нескольких языках, тысячи переведенными субтитрами загружены ежедневно. Бесплатно скачать из исходных текстов, поддержка API, миллионы пользователей.</description>
	<description lang="sk">Titulky pre filmy a TV seriály, denne nahratých tisíce titulkov preložených vo viacerých jazykoch. Sťahuj zadarmo zo zdroja, podpora API, milióny používateľov.</description>
	<description lang="sl">Filmski in televizijski podnapisi v mnogo jezikih, na tisoče prevedenih podnapisov dnevno. Brezplačen prenos iz vira, podpora API, miljoni uporabnikov.</description>
	<description lang="sq">Titra filmash dhe serialesh në shumë gjuhë, mijëra titra të përkthyera që vendosen çdo ditë. Shkarko nga burimi, apo nga mbështetja e API-së, miliona përdorues.</description>
	<description lang="sr">Titlovi za filmove i TV na mnogim jezicima, hiljade prevoda okačenih svakodnevno. Besplatno skidanje sa izvora, podrška za API, milioni korisnika.</description>
	<description lang="sv">Filmer och Tv-undertexter med olika språk, tusentals översatta undertexter uppladdade dagligen. Gratis nerladdning från källor, API support, miljoner av användare.</description>
	<description lang="tr">Her gün eklenen, pek çok dildeki binlerce film ve dizi altyazısı. Kaynağından ücretsiz indirme, API desteği ve milyonlarca kullanıcı.</description>
	<description lang="uz">Film va TV Taglavhalari ko'p tillarda, minglab tarjima qilingan taglavhalar har kuni tizimga yuklanadi. Bepul resursdan yuklab oling, API qo'llaydi, millionlab foydalanuvchilar.</description>
	<description lang="zh">多语种的电影及剧集字幕，每日更新千余条翻译好的字幕。免费下载，提供API接口，已拥有上百万的用户。</description>
    <disclaimer>Works without log-in</disclaimer>
	<news>
Improved add-on by OpenSubtitles.org
v5.2.14 (2017-01-23)
- Users are able to download subtitles as anonymous without authentication. Added localized descriptions, media files
- New feature: Users are able to check for subtitles when Kodi is not playing, by using the manual search or by standing on an item and opening the subtitles search dialog (By key or by an external addon)  | @burekas
	</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>https://forum.opensubtitles.org/viewtopic.php?f=8&amp;t=15847</forum>
    <website>http://www.opensubtitles.org</website>
    <email>admin [at] opensubtitles {dot} org</email>
	<assets>
	    <icon>resources/media/os_logo_512x512.png</icon>
	    <fanart>resources/media/os_fanart.jpg</fanart>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_1.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_2.jpg</screenshot>
		<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot_3.jpg</screenshot>
	</assets>
    <source>https://github.com/opensubtitles/service.subtitles.opensubtitles</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.requests" name="requests" version="2.27.1" provider-name="Python Software Foundation">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.certifi" version="2021.10.8"/>
    <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="4.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.idna" version="2.10.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.urllib3" version="1.26.9"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Requests is an elegant and simple HTTP library for Python, built for human beings.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Requests is an elegant and simple HTTP library for Python, built for human beings.</description>
    <license>Apache-2.0</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>https://requests.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/psf/requests</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyqrcode" version="0.0.2" name="pyQRcode" provider-name="Lunatixz">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_US">A Python interface to generate QR Code</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Una interfaz de Python para generar código QR</summary>
        <description lang="en_US">A Python interface to generate QR Code</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Una interfaz de Python para generar código QR</description>
        <forum></forum>
        <website>https://pypi.python.org/pypi/pyqrcode</website>
        <license>Apache2</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <source>https://github.com/Lunatixz/KODI_Addons/tree/master/script.module.pyqrcode</source>
        <news></news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.balandro" name="Balandro" version="4.0.00" provider-name="Team Balandro">
  <requires>
     <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
  </requires>

  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>

  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Balandro es un Navegador de páginas Webs</summary>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
    </assets>
    <news>
    [COLOR darkorange][B]Versión  [/COLOR][COLOR yellow]4.0.00[/COLOR][COLOR chartreuse]  Enero de 2024[/B][/COLOR]

    [COLOR goldenrod][B]Media Centers:[/B][/COLOR]
        [COLOR tan][B]Kodi Versiones Oficiales Soportadas:[/B][/COLOR]
        [COLOR plum][B]21.x Omega,  20.x Nexus,  19.x Matrix,[/B][/COLOR]
        [COLOR plum][B]18.x Leia  y  17.x Krypton[/B][/COLOR]

    [COLOR springgreen][B]Fuente[/COLOR]  [COLOR cyan]https://repobal.github.io/base/[/B][/COLOR]

    [COLOR firebrick][B]Team[/COLOR]  [COLOR orange]https://github.com/repobal[/B][/COLOR]

    [COLOR limegreen][B]Contacto:[/B][/COLOR]
        Foro  www.mimediacenter.info/foro/
        Telegram  t.me/balandro_asesor
        Team  t.me/Balandro_team

    [COLOR blue][B]Agradecimientos:[/B][/COLOR]
        Cita destacada a los miembros de Balandro Team
        Mención especial al grupo de Balandro Checkers

    [COLOR cyan][B]Canales:[/B][/COLOR]
        Revisión Generalizada
        Sin Novedades

    [COLOR fuchsia][B]Servidores:[/B][/COLOR]
        Revisión Generalizada
        Sin Novedades
    </news>
    <summary>Balandro es un Navegador de Páginas Webs</summary>
    <description>[COLOR moccasin][B]Navega con Kodi por Páginas Webs para poder ver sus contenidos de manera fácil. [COLOR yellow]Balandro es desde el año [COLOR cyan]2018[COLOR yellow] un MOD derivado de [COLOR yellowgreen]Pelisalacarta y Alfa[COLOR yellow],[COLOR mediumaquamarine] y tiene como objeto, permitir visualizar [COLOR deepskyblue]Películas[COLOR mediumaquamarine], [COLOR hotpink]Series[COLOR mediumaquamarine], [COLOR darkcyan]Documentales[COLOR mediumaquamarine], etc., todo a través de Internet y directamente desde su sistema Media Center. [COLOR orchid]Este Add-On es tan solo un mero Ejercicio de Aprendizaje del Lenguaje de Programación Python y se distribuye sin Ningún Contenido Multimedia adjunto al mismo [COLOR lightgrey][I]En consecuencia solo las Webs son Plenamente Responsables de los contenidos que publiquen.[/I][/B][/COLOR]</description>
    <disclaimer>[COLOR aqua][B]Los Propietarios y Distribuidores de este Add-On no Proveen ni Distribuyen Ningún Contenido Mostrado por el Add-On, ni Tienen Afiliación alguna con los Proveedores/Webs de contenidos. [COLOR tan]Está Prohibida su distribución, solo ó junto con Contenidos Multimedia Protegidos por los Derechos de Autor. [COLOR chocolate]Si este tipo de contenido está Prohibido en su País, solamente Usted será el Responsable de su uso. [COLOR white]La vulneración de estas prohibiciones Exonerarán de cualquier Culpa a sus Autores, [COLOR red]Siendo el unico Responsable quien lo haya Distribuido ó Utilizado Ilegalmente.[/B][/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GPL v3</license>
    <source>https://repobal.github.io/base/</source>
    <forum>https://www.mimediacenter.info/foro/</forum>
  </extension>

  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="services.py" start="login|startup"/>
</addon>

    <addon id="repository.masQelec" name="masQelec Repository" version="1.0.1" provider-name="masQelec">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="masQelec Repository">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/masQelec/repository.masQelec/master/addons/1.0/Amlogic/arm/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/masQelec/repository.masQelec/master/addons/1.0/Amlogic/arm/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/masQelec/repository.masQelec/master/addons/1.0/Amlogic/arm/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>masQelec Repository</summary>
		<description lang="en">The masQelec add-on repository contains Kodi PVR Clients and Servers, Screensavers, Visualisations, and more. Add-ons in this repository are maintained and supported by masQelec staff and YOU the community. If you find a broken or non-working add-on please report it via the forums, or help by submitting fixes via GitHub.</description>
		<description lang="es">El repositorio de complementos masQelec contiene clientes y servidores Kodi PVR, protectores de pantalla, visualizaciones y más. Los complementos en este repositorio son mantenidos y respaldados por el personal de masQelec y USTED la comunidad. Si encuentra un complemento roto o que no funciona, infórmelo a través de los foros o ayude enviando soluciones a través de GitHub.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
	    <assets>
      		<icon>icon.png</icon>
   	    </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pysocks" name="PySocks" version="1.6.8" provider-name="anorov">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.win_inet_pton" version="1.1.0" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">A SOCKS proxy client and wrapper for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">PySocks lets you send traffic through SOCKS and HTTP proxy servers. It is a modern fork of SocksiPy with bug fixes and extra features.</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Un cliente proxy SOCKS y un contenedor para Python</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">PySocks le permite enviar tráfico a través de SOCKS y servidores proxy HTTP. Es una bifurcación moderna de SocksiPy con correcciones de errores y características adicionales.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
## [1.6.8] - 2017-12-21
- Remove support for EOL Python 3.3

## [1.6.7] - 2017-03-22
- Make SocksiPy legacy functions kwarg-compatible. See issue [#71](https://github.com/Anorov/PySocks/pull/71).
- Use setuptools in setup.py to support wheel. See issue [#73](https://github.com/Anorov/PySocks/pull/73).
- Test and logging enhancements

## [1.6.6] - 2017-01-29
- Full test suite finally added
- Travis CI enabled for project
    </news>
    <language></language>
    <license>BSD</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://github.com/Anorov/PySocks</website>
    <source>https://github.com/dagwieers/script.module.pysocks</source>
    <email>dag@wieers.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.musicbrainz"
       name="Musicbrainz NGS webservice python bindings"
       version="0.6.0"
       provider-name="marcelveldt">
  <requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice</summary>
     <description lang="en">Kodi module library for the Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice developed by alastair.</description>
    <summary lang="es">Enlaces de Python para el servicio web NGS de Musicbrainz</summary>
     <description lang="es">Biblioteca del módulo Kodi para los enlaces de Python para el servicio web NGS de Musicbrainz desarrollado por alastair.</description>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
    <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.musicbrainz</source>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pil"
       name="Python Image Library"
       version="1.1.7"
       provider-name="PythonWare">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.epg.masqelec" name="Epg masQelec" version="0.0.4" provider-name="masQelec">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="autoexec.py">
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="es_ES">EPG masQelec mantiene actualizado tus canales.</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">EPG masQelec mantiene actualizado tus canales.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.urlresolver"
     name="URLResolver"
     version="2.10.0"
     provider-name="Eldorado">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.t0mm0.common" version="2.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
    <description lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
    <summary lang="es">Resuelva las URL de host de video comunes para que se puedan reproducir en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
    <description lang="es">Resuelva las URL de host de video comunes para que se puedan reproducir en XBMC / Kodi, simplifique el desarrollo de complementos de video que requieren múltiples hosts de video.</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.tvheadend42" name="Tvheadend Server 4.2" version="1.0.124" provider-name="masQelec">
  <requires><import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>

  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="download.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Tvheadend: a TV streaming server for Linux</summary>
    <description lang="en">Tvheadend (4.2.8-36): is a TV streaming server for Linux supporting DVB-S/S2, DVB-C, DVB-T/T2, IPTV, SAT>IP, ATSC and ISDB-T</description>
    <summary lang="es">Tvheadend: un servidor de transmisión de TV para Linux</summary>
    <description lang="es">Tvheadend (4.2.8-36): es un servidor de transmisión de TV para Linux compatible DVB-S/S2, DVB-C, DVB-T/T2, IPTV, SAT>IP, ATSC y ISDB-T</description>
    <disclaimer></disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
123
- update gnutls to 3.6.14

122
- update gnutls to 3.6.13

121
- update to 4.2.8-36
- update comskip to 2019-11-03
- fixed default recording path

120
- update to 4.2.8-27
- update comskip to 2019-03-30

119
- Use system libidn2

118
- update to 4.2.7-44
- fix tv_grab_file usage of &amp; in urls

117
- update to 4.2.7-34
- added hint to FRITZ!Box support (not needed anymore since FW 7.0)

116
- added comskip
- update to 4.2.6-62
- fix Tvheadend works now without network too
- fix for AVM IPs were not set correctly

115
- update to 4.2.6-7

114
- update to 4.2.5-31
- addded manual Scan-Table update

113
- update to 4.2.4-23
- full transcoding support

112
- update to 4.2.3-20
- changed name

111
- update to Tvheadend 4.2.2-75

110
- added tv_grab_file support for compressed files (gz bz2 xz)
- update to Tvheadend 4.2.1.7
- fix FRITZ!Box support, AVM Repeater and 6490 are now working

109
- added custom start options to addon
- added FRITZ!Box Sat&amp;gt;IP server support to addon
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2415
- fix debug if activated but nothing selected

108
- added CA (libdvben50221) support
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2401

107
- rebuild due ssl change

106
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2309
- service gets restarted at changes in add-on settings
- improved Tvh defaults

105
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2236
- fixes picons download from Tvh server
- fixes empty/incomplete frequency scan-tables

104
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2195
- added TRACE debug option at the addon config

103
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.2134

102
- update for LibreELEC 8.0
- update to Tvheadend 4.1.1945
- fix the XMLTV import script

100
- initial LibreELEC version
    </news>
    <assets><icon>resources/icon.png</icon><fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.png</screenshot>

    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.cherrypy"
       name="CherryPy Kodi module"
       version="11.0.1"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, CherryPy Team">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">CherryPy webserver packaged as Kodi module</summary>
        <description lang="en">CherryPy is a pythonic, object-oriented web framework
            CherryPy allows developers to build web applications in much the same way they would build any other object-oriented Python program. This results in smaller source code developed in less time.
            CherryPy is now more than ten years old and it is has proven to be very fast and stable. It is being used in production by many sites, from the simplest to the most demanding.
        </description>
		<summary lang="es">Servidor web CherryPy empaquetado como módulo Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="es">CherryPy es un marco web pitónico orientado a objetos
            CherryPy permite a los desarrolladores crear aplicaciones web de la misma manera que crearía cualquier otro programa Python orientado a objetos. Esto da como resultado un código fuente más pequeño desarrollado en menos tiempo.
            CherryPy tiene ahora más de diez años y ha demostrado ser muy rápido y estable. Está siendo utilizado en producción por muchos sitios, desde los más simples hasta los más exigentes.
        </description>
        <license>BSD</license>
        <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.cherrypy</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplejson"
       name="simplejson"
       version="3.16.1"
       provider-name="Bob Ippolito">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <summary lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Code taken from https://pypi.org/project/simplejson/</disclaimer>
	<summary lang="es">Codificador/decodificador JSON simple, rápido y extensible para Python</summary>
    <description lang="es">Codificador/decodificador JSON simple, rápido y extensible para Python</description>
    <disclaimer lang="es">Código tomado de https://pypi.org/project/simplejson/</disclaimer>
    <license>MIT License, Academic Free License v. 2.1</license>
    <website>https://pypi.org/project/simplejson/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/simplejson/simplejson</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.future"
       name="future"
       version="0.17.1"
       provider-name="Ed Schofield">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="libs" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Clean single-source support for Python 3 and 2</summary>
    <description lang="en">future is the missing compatibility layer between Python 2 and Python 3. It allows you to use a single, clean Python 3.x-compatible codebase to support both Python 2 and Python 3 with minimal overhead.</description>
	<summary lang="es">Soporte limpio de fuente única para Python 3 y 2</summary>
    <description lang="es">El futuro es la capa de compatibilidad que falta entre Python 2 y Python 3. Le permite utilizar una base de código única y limpia compatible con Python 3.x para admitir tanto Python 2 como Python 3 con una sobrecarga mínima.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/PythonCharmers/python-future</source>
    <website>http://python-future.org</website>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.linuxserver.docker" name="LinuxServer.io's Docker Add-ons" version="9.0.102.102" provider-name="LinuxServer.io">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="LinuxServer.io's Docker Add-on Repository">
    <info compressed="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/linuxserver/libreelec-addon-repo/master/addons.xml</info>
    <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/linuxserver/libreelec-addon-repo/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
    <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/linuxserver/libreelec-addon-repo/master/download</datadir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Install add-ons from LinuxServer.io's docker repository</summary>
    <description>
Download and install docker container add-ons from the LinuxServer.io repository.

Please visit https://linuxserver.io for more information.
    </description>
    <disclaimer> </disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
101
- Change repo location for zips

100
- Initial LibreELEC version
    </news>
    <assets><icon>resources/icon.png</icon><fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>

    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.t0mm0.common"
	     name="t0mm0's common stuff"
	     version="2.1.1"
	     provider-name="t0mm0">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
    <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.samsung.tv.plus" name="Samsung TV Plus" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.1.8">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Just free TV. Whether you're a news buff, sports fan, gamer, an aspiring chef, or need something for the kids, Samsung TV Plus offers TV that everyone can enjoy.</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Move EPG url into Playlist</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pydes"
       name="pyDes"
       version="2.0.1"
       provider-name="Todd Whiteman">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">A pure python module which implements the DES and Triple-DES encryption algorithms.</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Un módulo de Python puro que implementa los algoritmos de cifrado DES y Triple-DES.</summary>
    <website>http://twhiteman.netfirms.com/des.html</website>
    <license>Public Domain</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <source>http://sourceforge.net/projects/pydes/</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="5.14.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="skin" schema="skin.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.win_inet_pton" name="win-inet-pton" version="1.1.0" provider-name="hickeroar">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Native python inet_pton implementation on Windows (with ctypes)</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Native inet_pton and inet_ntop implementation for Python on Windows (with ctypes).</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Implementación nativa de python inet_pton en Windows (con ctypes)</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Implementación nativa de inet_pton e inet_ntop para Python en Windows (con ctypes).</description>
    <platform>windows</platform>
    <language></language>
    <license>Public Domain</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://github.com/hickeroar/win_inet_pton</website>
    <source>https://github.com/dagwieers/script.module.win_inet_pton</source>
    <email>dag@wieers.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.bottle" name="Bottle" version="0.12.17" provider-name="Marcel Hellkamp">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="kodi.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Fast and simple WSGI-framework for small web-applications</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Bottle is a fast and simple micro-framework for small web applications. It offers request dispatching (Routes) with url parameter support, templates, a built-in HTTP Server and adapters for many third party WSGI/HTTP-server and template engines - all in a single file and with no dependencies other than the Python Standard Library.</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Marco WSGI rápido y simple para pequeñas aplicaciones web</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Bottle es un micro marco rápido y simple para pequeñas aplicaciones web. Ofrece despacho de solicitudes (rutas) con soporte de parámetros de url, plantillas, un servidor HTTP incorporado y adaptadores para muchos motores de plantillas y servidores WSGI / HTTP de terceros, todo en un solo archivo y sin dependencias distintas de la biblioteca estándar de Python .</description>
	<license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/bottlepy/bottle</source>
    <website>http://bottlepy.org</website>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.image.resource.select" name="Image Resource Select Addon" version="2.0.4" provider-name="ronie">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Image resource selection addon</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Script for skinners to let users select an image resource addon.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Complemento de selección de recursos de imagen</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Script para skinners para permitir a los usuarios seleccionar un complemento de recursos de imagen.</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=239558</forum>
		<source>https://gitlab.com/ronie/script.image.resource.select</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.thetvdb"
       name="The TVDB API v2"
       version="1.0.27"
       provider-name="marcelveldt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</summary>
		<description lang="en">TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</description>
        <summary lang="es">El módulo Python de TVDB API v2 para Kodi</summary>
		<description lang="es">El módulo Python de TVDB API v2 para Kodi</description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.thetvdb</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simple.downloader" name="Simple Downloader for xbmc plugins" provider-name="TheCollective" version="1.9.5">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.1" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.service" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Simple downloader for xbmc plugins.</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Descargador simple para complementos kodi.</summary>
  </extension>
  <extension library="lib" point="xbmc.python.module" />
</addon>

<addon id="repository.xbmc.org"
		name="Kodi Add-on repository"
               version="9.9.0"
		provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
  </requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository">
		<!-- Do not forget to bump add-on version when changing paths to force a repo refresh -->
               <info>https://addons.coreelec.org/leia/addons.xml.gz</info>
               <checksum verify="sha256">https://addons.coreelec.org/leia/addons.xml.gz?sha256</checksum>
               <datadir>https://addons.coreelec.org/leia</datadir>
               <artdir>https://addons.coreelec.org/leia</artdir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Installeer Byvoegsels vanaf Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="am_ET">ከ Kodi.tv ተጨማ-ሪዎች መግጠሚያ </summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">ثبت إضافات من موقع Kodi.tv الرسمي</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Усталяваць дадатак з Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Инсталира добавки от Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Instal·la complements des de Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Instalovat doplňky z Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="cy_GB">Gosod Ychwanegion o Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Installer add-ons fra Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Installiere Addons von Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Εγκατάσταση Προσθέτων από το Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Install Add-ons from Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Install Add-ons from Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Install Add-ons from Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Install Add-ons from Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Instalar Add-ons de Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Instalar Add-ons de Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Installar Add-ons de Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Paigalda lisasid Kodi.tv lehelt</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Instalatu Kodi.tv-eko gehigarriak</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">‫نصف افزونه‌ها از Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Asenna lisäosia Kodi.tv -sivustolta</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Installer des addiciels depuis Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Installer des extensions depuis Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Instalar complementos dende Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">התקנת הרחבות מ־Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Instaliraj dodatke s Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Kiegészítők letöltése az Kodi.tv-ról</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Pasang Pengaya dari Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Setja inn viðbætur frá Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Installa addon da Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Kodi.tv からアドオンをインストール</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">Kodi.tv에서 애드온 설치</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Įdiegti priedus iš Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Instalēt pielikumus no Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Инсталирај Додатоци од Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Pasang tambahan daripada Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="mt_MT">Installa Add-ons minn Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="my_MM">Kodi.tv မှ Add-on များကိုသွင်းမည်</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Installer utvidelser fra Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Add-ons van Kodi.tv installeren</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Instaluj dodatki z Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Instale Add-ons do Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Instalar Add-ons a partir de Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Instalați suplimente de la Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Установить дополнения с сайта Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Inštalovať doplnky z Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Namestite dodatke s Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Инсталирај додатне програме са Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Instaliraj dodatne programe sa Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Installera tillägg från Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Insztaluj przidŏwki ze Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="tg_TJ">Насб кардани барномаҳои иловагӣ аз Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">ติดตั้งส่วนเสริมจาก Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Kodi.tv sitesinden eklentileri yükle</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Встановити додатки з Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Cài đặt Add-on từ Kodi.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">从 Kodi.tv 安装插件</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">從 Kodi.tv 安裝附加元件</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Aflaai en installeer byvoegsels vanaf die Amptelike Kodi.tv byvoegsel kodebank.[CR] Deur die amptelike Kodebank te gebruik trek jy voordeel van ons uitgebreide lêer spieël diens wat jou help vinniger aflaai vanaf 'n gebied naby aan jou.[CR] Alle byvoegsels in die kodebank het basiese toetsing ondergaan, as jy 'n gebreekte of nie werkende byvoegsel vind rapporteer dit asseblief aan die Kodi Span sodat ons die nodige stappe kan neem.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">حمل و ثبت الإضافات من مستودع الإضافات لموقع Kodi.tv الرسمي.[CR] باستخدامك المستودع الرسمي ستكون قادر على الاستفادة مما نقدمه من خدمة حصرية لتوفير خوادم بديله لتحميل الملفات توفر لك سرعة تحميل أعلى من منطقه قريبة منك.[CR] جميع الإضافات في هذا المستودع خضعت لاختبارات مبدئية, إذا صادفتك إضافة معطوبة أو لا تعمل برجاء الإبلاغ عنها لفريق Kodi لنتمكن من اتخاذ الإجراء اللازم.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Спампаваць і ўсталяваць дадатак з афіцыйнага рэпазітара Kodi.tv . [CR] Пры выкарыстанні афіцыйнага рэпазітара вы зможаце скарыстацца нашым сэрвісам люстэрак, каб у вас была больш хуткая спампоўка з рэгіёна, бліжэйшага да вас . [CR] Усе дадаткі ў гэтым рэпазітары былі пратэставаныя, калі вы выявілі зламаны ці не працуючы дадатак, калі ласка, паведаміце пра гэта камандзе Kodi, каб мы маглі гэта выправіць.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Сваля и инсталира добавки от официалното хранилище за добавки на Kodi.tv. Ползвайки добавката ще се възползвате от системата ни от огледални сървъри - за да сваляте с висока скорост, от сървър близък до Вас. Добавките от хранилището са минали няколко теста, но ако се натъкнете на неработеща или проблемна добавка, моля уведомете екипа на Kodi, за да бъдат предприети необходимите действия.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Baixeu i instal·leu els complements des del dipòsit oficial de Kodi.tv.[CR] Mitjançant el dipòsit oficial, podreu aprofitar els avantatges del nostre servei de rèplica de fitxers per ajudar-vos a tenir unes baixades més ràpides des d'una regió que estigui a prop vostre.[CR] Tots els complements d'aquest dipòsit han passat per proves bàsiques, així que si trobeu algun complement que no funcioni correctament, si us plau, digueu-ho a l'equip de Kodi perquè puguin dur a terme les accions pertinents.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Stáhnout a nainstalovat doplňky z oficiálního repozitáře doplňků Kodi.tv.[CR] Použitím oficiálního repozitáře budete moci využít naši rozsáhlou službu zrcadel souborů, která vám pomůže rychleji stahovat z oblasti blízko vás.[CR] Všechny doplňky v tomto repozitáři prošly základním testováním. Pokud najdete rozbitý nebo nefunkční doplněk, oznamte to týmu Kodi, abychom mohli přijmout veškerá nezbytná opatření.</description>
		<description lang="cy_GB">Llwytho i lawr a gosod ychwanegion o storfa ychwanegion Swyddogol Kodi.tv.{CR}Drwy ddefnyddio'r Storfa swyddogol bydd modd i chi gymryd mantais o'n gwasanaeth drychau ffeiliau i'ch cynorthwyoi lwytho i lawr yn gyflym o ardal yn agos i chi.[CR] Mae pob ychwnaegyn yn y storfa hwn wedi eu profi'n fras, os ydych yn canfod ychwanegyn sydd wedi torri  neu ddim yn gweithio yna hysbyswch Team Kodi fel bod modd i ni weithredu.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Hent og installer add-ons fra det officielle Kodi.tv add-on fjernlager.[CR] Ved at bruge det officielle fjernlager drager du fordel af vores omfattende spejltjeneste, som gør at du kan hente hurtigere fra et sted nær dig.[CR]  Alle add-ons i dette fjernlager har gennemgået grundlæggende tests. Hvis du finder en defekt add-on, så rapporter venligst dette til Team Kodi, så vi kan tage hånd i hanke med eventuelle problemer.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Dies ist das offizielle Kodi.tv Addon-Verzeichnis.[CR]Dieses Addon-Verzeichnis ermöglicht aufgrund umfangreicher Spiegelserver in der Nähe schnelle Downloads.[CR]Alle Addons in diesem Verzeichnis wurden einfachen Tests unterzogen. Sollte dennoch ein Addon nicht richtig funktionieren benachrichtige bitte Team Kodi, damit wir reagieren können.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Πραγματοποιήστε λήψη και εγκατάσταση προσθέτων από το επίσημο αποθετήριο του Kodi.tv.[CR]  Χρησιμοποιώντας το Επίσημο Αποθετήριο μπορείτε να εκμεταλλευτείτε τους εκτεταμένους διακομιστές αρχείων μας για ταχύτερες λήψεις από μία κοντινή σας περιοχή.[CR]  Όλα τα πρόσθετα σε αυτό το αποθετήριο έχουν περάσει τις στοιχειώδεις δοκιμές, αν βρείτε ένα κατεστραμμένο ή ανενεργό πρόσθετο παρακαλούμε να το αναφέρετε στην Ομάδα Kodi ούτως ώστε να πραγματοποιηθούν οι απαραίτητες ενέργειες.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Download and install add-ons from the Official Kodi.tv add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have undergone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team Kodi so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Download and install add-ons from the Official Kodi.tv add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team Kodi so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Download and install add-ons from the Official Kodi.tv add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team Kodi so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Download and install add-ons from the Official Kodi.tv add-on repository.[CR]  By using the official Repository you will be able to take advantage of our extensive file mirror service to help get you faster downloads from a region close to you.[CR]  All add-ons on this repository have under gone basic testing, if you find a broken or not working add-on please report it to Team Kodi so we can take any action needed.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Descarga e instala el complemento desde el repositorio oficial de Kodi.tv.[CR] Usando el repositorio oficial tendrá las ventajas de nuestro servicio de réplicas para ayudarle a conseguir unas descargas más rápidas de un sitio cercano a su región.[CR] Todos los complementos en este repositorio han pasado por un periodo de pruebas básico, pero si encuentra algún complemento que no funciona, por favor infórmelo al equipo de Kodi para que podamos tomar las acciones necesarias.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Descarga e instala add-ons desde el repositorio oficial de Kodi.[CR]  Usando el repositorio oficial podrá aprovecharse de nuestro servicio de mirrors para poder descargar más rápidamente desde un sitio cercano.[CR]  Todos los add-ons de este repositorio han pasado por un periodo de pruebas básico, pero si encontrara alguno que no funcionase, por favor, avise al equipo de Kodi para solucionar el problema.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Descarga e instala add-ons del repositorio oficial Kodi.tv.[CR] Al usar el repositorio oficial, tendrá la ventaja de los servicios de espejos, y así tener descargas más rápidas.[CR] Todos los add-ons en este repositorio se han probado de manera básica, si encuentra alguno que no funciona o roto, favor de reportarlo al Equipo de Kodi para poder tomar las medidas necesarias.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Lae alla ja installi lisasid ametlikust Kodi.tv hoidlast.[CR]  Ametliku hoidla kasutamise eeliseks on võimalus kasutada meie ulatuslikku failide peegelteenust laadides faile sulle kõige lähemast serverist.[CR]  Kõik lisad selles hoidlas on läbinud elementaarse testimise. Siiski, kui sa leiad vigase või mittetöötava lisa, siis palun teavita sellest Kodi meeskonda, et me saaksime vajaliku abi osutada.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Deskargatu eta instalatu gehigarriak Kodi.tv biltegi ofizialetik.[CR]  &amp;#10;Biltegi ofiziala erabiliz zugandik gertu dagoen gune batetik deskargatu&amp;#10;ditzakezu gure fitxategi-ispilu zerbitzu zabalaren abantailaz aprobetxatuaz.[CR]  &amp;#10;Biltegi honetako gehigarri guztiek oinarrizko probak gainditu dituzte baina hondaturiko edo funtzionatzen ez duen gehigarri baten bat aurkituz gero jakinarazi Kodi taldeari beharrezko ekintzak burutu ditzagun.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">افزودنی ها را از منبع رسمی افزونه ها در Kodi.tv دانلود و نصب کنید. [CR] با استفاده از منبع رسمی شما قادر خواهید بود از خدمات گسترده سرویس دانلود جایگزین ما بهره ببرید که امکان دانلود از مناطق نزدیکتر را در اختیار شما قرار می دهد. [CR] همه افزونه های این منبع آزمایش های اولیه را پشت سر گذاشته اند. در صورت یافتن افزونه معیوب یا غیر قابل استفاده لطفا آن را به تیم کودی گزارش کنید تا اقدامات لازم را انجام دهیم.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Lataa ja asenna lisäosia virallisesta Kodi.tv lisäosien ohjelmavarastosta.[CR]  Käyttämällä virallista ohjelmavarastoa sinun on mahdollista käyttää hyväksesi meidän kattavaa tiedostojen peilauspalveluamme saavuttaaksesi korkeat latausnopeudet sinun lähialueeltasi.[CR]  Kaikki tämän ohjelmavaraston lisäosat on testattu toimiviksi, jos löydät rikkinäisen tai "ei toimivan" lisäosan, ilmoita siitä Team Kodille, jotta voimme korjata asian.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Télécharger et installer des addiciels depuis le dépôt officiel de Kodi.tv.[CR] En utilisant le dépôt officiel vous pourrez bénéficier de notre service étendu de miroirs de fichiers favorisant des téléchargements plus rapides depuis une région proche de vous.[CR] Tous les addiciels de ce dépôt ont subi des tests de base. Si vous trouvez un addiciel non fonctionnel ou brisé, veuillez le rapporter à l’équipe Kodi afin que nous puissions agir.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Télécharger et installer des extensions à partir du dépôt officiel Kodi.tv.[CR]En utilisant le dépôt officiel, vous bénéficierez de notre service de serveurs miroirs permettant de télécharger rapidement depuis une région proche de chez vous.[CR]Toutes les extensions de ce dépôt ont subi des tests de base, si vous trouvez une extension totalement ou en partie inutilisable, merci d'en informer l'Équipe Kodi afin que nous puissions prendre les mesures nécessaires.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Descargar e instalar complementos dende o repositorio oficial de Kodi.tv.[CR] Empregando o repositorio oficial, poderás gozar das vantaxes do seu extenso servizo de replicación de ficheiros que che permite unhas descargas máis rápidas dende unha rexión preto á túa.[CR] Tódolos complementos deste repositorio pasaron por comprobacións básicas. Se atopas algún complemento roto ou non funcional, por favor informa ao equipo de Kodi para que poidan actuar en consecuencia.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">הורדה והתקנת הרחבות ממאגר הרחבות Kodi.tv הרשמי.[CR] שימוש במאגר הרשמי מאפשר לנצל את שירות שיקוף הקבצים של Kodi.tv העוזר להוריד מהר יותר מהשרת הקרוב ביותר.[CR] כל ההרחבות במאגר זה עברו בדיקה בסיסית. יש לדווח לצוות הפיתוח של Kodi על כל הרחבה שנמצאה כלא תקינה או שלא עובדת ע"מ שתתבצע הפעולה המתאימה.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Preuzmite i instalirajte dodatke sa službenog Kodi.tv repozitorija dodataka.[CR] Korištenjem službenog repozitorija bit ćete u mogućnosti iskoristiti prednosti usluge našeg brzog zrcalnog poslužitelja datoteka, kako bi mogli brže preuzimati iz regije koje je bliže vašoj lokaciji.[CR] Svi dodaci na ovom repozitoriju prošli su osnovno testiranje, u slučaju da primijetite neispravan dodatak, molimo vas da to prijavite Kodi timu koji će zatim poduzeti potrebne korake.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Kiegészítők letöltése és telepítése a hivatalos Kodi.tv tárolóhelyről.[CR] A hivatalos tárolóhely használatával kihasználhatod szerteágazó tükör-kiszolgáló hálózatunkat, ami segít a gyorsabb letöltésben egy hozzád közelebb eső körzet használatával.[CR]  Minden kiegészítő ezen a tárolóhelyen átment egy alaptesztelésen. Ha mégis hibás vagy nem működő kiegészítőt találsz, kérünk jelezd az Kodi csapatnak, hogy megtegyük a szükséges lépéseket.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Unduh dan pasang pengaya dari repositori pengaya resmi Kodi.tv. [CR] Dengan menggunakan repositori resmi anda akan mendapat keuntungan dari miror berkas kami yang luas dimana dapat membantu anda untuk lebih cepat mengunduh dari daerah yang dekat dengan anda. [CR] Semua pengaya pada repository telah melalui uji coba standar, jika anda menemukan pengaya yang rusak atau tidak bekerja tolong laporkan kepada tim Kodi agar kami bisa menindak lanjutinya.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Sækja og setja inn viðbætur frá hinu viðurkennda Kodi.tv viðbótasafni.[CR] Með því að nota þetta safn getur þú nýtt þér möguleikann á fullkominni speglunarþjónustu sem hjálpar við að sækja hraðar viðbætur frá landsvæði nálægt þér.[CR] Allar viðbætur í þessu safni hafa gengið undir grunnprófanir, ef þú finnur viðbætur sem eru bilaðar eða virka ekki, endilega láttu Kodi-teymið vita svo við getum gert eitthvað í málinu.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Scarica e installa gli add-on dalla libreria ufficiale di Kodi.tv.[CR]  Usando la libreria ufficiale avrai il vantaggio di ottenere download più veloci con mirror più vicini alla tua località.[CR]  Tutti gli add-on in questa libreria sono stati sottoposti a test di base, se ne trovi uno non funzionante o corrotto, per favore riporta il problema al team di Kodi così potremmo prendere provvedimenti.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">オフィシャルの Kodi.tv リポジトリからアドオンをダウンロードします。[CR]  オフィシャルリポジトリを使うことで、お住まいのエリアに近いミラーサーバーから高速にアドオンをダウンロードすることが可能です。[CR]  このリポジトリ上のアドオンは全て、簡単な動作テストを受けてはいますが、もしアドオンがおかしかったりうまく動作しなかったりした場合は、Kodi チームに連絡をお願いします。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">공식 Kodi.tv 애드온 저장소에서 애드온을 다운로드하여 설치합니다.[CR] 공식 저장소를 사용하면 파일 미러링 서비스를 통해 사용자와 가까운 곳에서 빠르게 다운로드할 수 있습니다.[CR] 저장소의 모든 애드온은 기본 테스트를 거치지만 작동이 되지 않거나 손상된 애드온을 발견하면 필요한 조치를 취할 수 있게 Team Kodi로 알려주시기 바랍니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Atsisiųskite ir įdiegite priedus iš oficialios Kodi.tv saugyklos.[CR]Naudojantis oficialia saugykla, galėsite pasinaudoti pranašumu mūsų didele failų veidrodinę paslauga.[CR]Taip pat siekiame padėti jums greičiau parsisiųsti priedą iš Jūsų regiono.[CR]Visiems šioje saugykloje saugomiems priedams buvo atliktas testavimas, jei Jūs radote netaisyklingą ir nedarbinį priedą.[CR]Prašome pranešti apie tai Kodi komandai, kad mes galėtume imtis būtinų veiksmų </description>
		<description lang="lv_LV">Lejupielādējiet un instalējiet pielikumus no oficiālā Kodi.tv pielikumu repozitorija[CR] Izmantojot oficiālo repozitoriju, varēsiet izmantot mūsu plašo spoguļu pakalpojumu, lai iegūtu ātrākas lejupielādes no reģiona, kas vistuvāk.[CR] Visi pielikumi šajā repozitorijā ir izgājuši pamata testēšanu, bet, ja atrodat saplīsušu vai nestrādājošu pielikumu, lūdzu, ziņojiet par to Team Kodi, lai varam izpildīt nepieciešamās labošanas darbības.</description>
		<description lang="mk_MK">Превземи и инсталирај Додатоци од официјалниот Kodi.tv склад.[CR] Со користење на официјалниот склад ќе бидете во можност да ги користите предностите на нашата богата датотека со услуги која ви помага да добиете побрзи превземања од регионот блиску до вас.[CR]  Сите Додатоци во овој склад се основно тестирани, ако најдете неисправни или додатоци кои не работат пријавете го тоа на тимот на Kodi така што ќе можеме да превземеме било каква акција што е потребна.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Muat turun dan pasang tambahan PVR melalui repositori rasmi Kodi.tv[CR]  Dengan menggunakan Repositori rasmi anda dapat perkhidmatan cermin fail yang luas supaya dapat memuat turun lebih pantas menerusi kawasan berhampiran anda.[CR]  Semua tambahan di dalam repositori ini telah lulus pengujian asas, jika anda temui tambahan yang rosak atau tidak berfungsi sila laporkannya kepada Team Kodi supaya kami boleh membuat tindakan yang sewajarnya.</description>
		<description lang="mt_MT">Niżżel u nstalla add-ons mir-repożitorju uffiċjali ta Kodi.tv.[CR] Permezz ta' dan ir-ripożitorju uffiċjali tista' tieħu vantaġġ mis-servizz ta' file mirrors estensiv li jgħinek tniżżel l-add-ons iktar malajr minn postijiet li huma ġeografikament qrib tiegħek.[CR] L-Add-ons kollha f'dan ir-repożitorju għaddew minn testijiet bażiċi, f'każ li tinzerta xi add-on miksura jew mhux taħdem jekk jpgħġbok irrportha lil Team Kodi biex inkunu nistgħu nieħdu l-azzjoni li jkun hemm bżonn.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Last ned og installer utvidelser fra den offisielle Kodi.tv-pakkebrønnen.[CR] Når du benytter den offisielle pakkebrønnen kan du dra nytte av vår omfattende arkivtjeneste slik at du får raskere nedlasting fra en tjener nær deg.[CR] Alle tillegg i denne brønnen har gått gjennom grunnleggende testing, men hvis du finner en utvidelse som ikke fungerer, rapporter det til Team Kodi, så vi får sett på det.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Download en installeer add-ons uit de officiële Kodi.tv add-on depot.[CR]Wanneer u de officiële depot gebruikt beschikt u over onze uitgebreide mirrorservice, waardoor u snel kunt downloaden van locaties in uw buurt.[CR] Alle add-ons in dit depot ondergingen standaardtests. Indien u een defecte of niet-werkende add-on vindt, meld dit dan aan Team Kodi zodat zij actie kunnen ondernemen.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Pobieraj i instaluj dodatki z oficjalnego repozytorium Kodi.tv.[CR] Używając oficjalnego repozytorium korzystasz z serwerów lustrzanych, rozsianych po całym świecie. Wybierany jest ten, który znajduje się najbliżej ciebie, zapewniając dużą prędkość połączenia.[CR]Wszystkie dodatki znajdujące się w tym repozytorium są testowane, ale mogą okazać się niesprawne. Zgłoś wówczas błąd, aby zespół Kodi mógł podjąć odpowiednie działanie.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Transfira e instale add-ons a partir do repositório oficial do Kodi.tv.[CR]|Ao utilizar o repositório oficial, você será capaz de tirar proveito do nosso serviço de espelhamento de arquivos, auxiliando em downloads mais rápidos a partir de uma região perto de você.[CR]|Todos os add-ons neste repositório passam por testes básicos, se você encontrar algum quebrado ou que não esteja funcionando, por favor reporte para a equipe do Kodi, para que possamos tomar as ações necessárias.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Transferir e instalar add-ons a partir do repositório de add-ons oficiais de Kodi.tv.[CR]Ao utilizar o Repositório oficial, irá beneficiar do nosso serviço de servidores de ficheiros para o ajudar a ter transferências mais rápidas da região mais perto de si.[CR]Todos os Add-ons neste repositório foram alvo de testes básicos. Se encontrar um danificado ou que não funciona, por favor, informe Tema Kodi, para que a situação seja resolvida.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Descărcați și instalați suplimente din depozitul de suplimente Kodi.tv oficial.[CR]  Folosind depozitul (repository) oficial puteți beneficia de serviciul nostru de găzduire distribuită pentru a vă ajuta să descărcați mai repede dintr-o regiune mai apropiată de dumneavoastră.[CR]  Toate suplimentele din acest depozit au trecut testele de bază, în caz că găsiți un supliment defect vă rugăm să îl raportați echipei Kodi pentru a lua măsurile necesare.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Загружайте и устанавливайте обновления из официального репозитория Kodi.tv[CR]Используя официальный репозиторий, вы сможете воспользоваться преимуществами распределенного хранилища для быстрой загрузки файлов с ближайшего к вам сервера.[CR]Все дополнения в данном репозитории прошли тестирование. Если вы обнаружили нерабочее дополнение, сообщите об этом разработчикам Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Stiahnuť a nainštalovať doplnky z oficiálneho zdroja doplnkov Kodi.tv.[CR] Použitím oficiálneho zdroja získavate možnosť využiť rozsiahly systém serverov, ktorý Vám umožní rýchlejšie sťahovanie z vám blízkeho regiónu.[CR] Všetky doplnky v tomto zdroji boli podrobené základnému testovaniu. Ak nájdete poškodené alebo nefunkčné doplnky, oznámte to prosím týmu Kodi aby mohol podľa potreby zakročiť.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Prenos in namestitev dodatkov iz uradnega skladišča Kodi.tv.[CR] Z uporabo uradnega skladišča, boste lahko izkoristili hitrejšo povezavo, ki bo izbrana glede na vašo lokacijo.[CR] Vsi dodatki tega skladišča so bili osnovno stestirani, če pa boste našli pokvarjen ali nedelujoč dodatek, to sporočite ekipi Kodi, da bomo lahko odpravili napake.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Преузмите и инсталирајте додатке из Званичног Kodi.tv спремишта додатака.[CR] Коришћењем званичног Спремишта моћићете да искористите предности нашег сервиса копија фајлова који ће вам помоћи приликом бржег преузимања из региона ближег вашој локацији.[CR] Сви додаци у овом спремишту прошли су основно тестирање, у случају да пронађете неисправан додатак молимо вас да то пријавите Kodi тиму који ће затим предузети неопходне мере.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Preuzmi i instaliraj dodatne programe iz Zvaničnog Kodi.tv spremišta za dodatne programe.[CR] Korišćenjem zvaničnog Spremišta moći ćete da iskoristite prednosti našeg servisa kopija fajlova koji će vam pomoći prilikom bržeg preuzimanja iz regiona bližeg vašoj lokaciji.[CR] Svi dodatni programi u ovom spremištu prošli su osnovno testiranje, u slučaju da pronađete neispravan dodatni program molimo vas da to prijavite Kodi timu koji će zatim preduzeti neophodne mere.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Ladda ner och installera tillägg från det officiella Kodi.tv tilläggsförrådet.[CR] Genom att använda det officiella förrådet kommer du att få fördelen att kunna använda vår omfattande spegeltjänst som kommer att hjälpa dig till snabbare nedladdningar från en plats nära dig.[CR] Alla tillägg i detta förråd har genomgått grundläggande tester. Hittar du ett trasigt eller icke fungerande tillägg, vänligen meddela detta till Team Kodi så att vi kan vidta nödvändiga åtgärder.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Sebiyrej i insztaluj przidŏwki z ôficjalnygo repozytoriōm Kodi.tv.[CR] Przi Używaniu ôficjalnygo repozytoriōm używŏsz serwerōw zdrzadłowych, rozsianych po calistym świecie. Ôbiyrany je tyn, kery je nŏjbliżyj ciebie, co istuje srogõ wartkość skuplowaniŏ.[CR]Wszyjske przidŏwki w tym repozytoriōm sōm testowane, ale mogōm pokŏzać sie popszniōne. Zgłoś wtynczŏs feler, coby ekipa Kodi mogła go sprŏwić.</description>
		<description lang="tg_TJ">Барномаҳои иловагиро аз анбори нармафзори Kodi.tv боргирӣ кунед ва насб намоед.[CR]  Аз истифодаи анбори нармафзори расмии мо ба шумо имконият пайдо мешавад, ки тавонед шароити мусофидро аз хидмати оинаи файлии васеъ ба даст оред ва нармафзори лозимиро аз сервери минтакаи ба шумо наздиктар бо суръати баланд боргирӣ кунед.[CR]  Ҳамаи барномаҳо аз анбори нармафзори мо дар ҳолати санҷишӣ мебошанд, бинобар ин агар ягон барномаи иловагии нуқсондор ё вайроншударо ёбед, лутфан дар бораи он барнома ва нуқсон пайдошуда ба гурӯҳи кории Kodi гузориш диҳед, то ин ки мо тавонем ҳамаи камбудиҳои барномаҳои моро ҳал кунем.</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">ดาวน์โหลดและติดตั้งส่วนเสริม จากแหล่งข้อมูลโปรแกรมของ Kodi.tv อย่างเป็นทางการ.[CR]  โดยการใช้งานแหล่งข้อมูลโปรแกรมอย่างเป็นทางการ คุณสามารถใช้ประโยชน์จากบริการแฟ้มมิเรอร์ที่กว้างขวางของเรา ที่จะช่วยให้การดาวน์โหลดของคุณเร็วขึ้นจากภูมิภาคที่ใกล้ที่สุด.[CR]  ส่วนเสริม ทั้งหมดในแหล่งเก็บข้อมูลนี้ อยู่ภายใต้การทดสอบขั้นพื้นฐานแล้ว ถ้าคุณพบส่วนเสริมที่เสียหายหรือไม่ทำงาน กรุณาแจ้งทีมงาน Kodi เพื่อให้เราสามารถดำเนินการใด ๆ ที่จำเป็น.</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Eklentileri resmi Kodi.tv eklenti deposundan indir ve yükle.[CR]Resmi yazılım depomuzu kullanarak size en yakın bölgeden en hızlı biçimde indirme yapmanızı sağlayacak gelişkin dosya aynalama servisini kullanma avantajını elde edeceksiniz.[CR]Bu yazılım deposundaki tüm eklentiler temel testlerden geçerler, şayet hatalı ya da çalışmayan bir eklenti bulur iseniz lütfen düzeltilmesi için bu durumu Kodi Takımına bildiriniz.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Завантажити і встановити додатки з Офіційного репозиторію додатків Kodi.tv.[CR]  Використовуючи Офіційний Репозиторій ви отримаєте перевагу надану нашими дзеркальними серверами, які забезпечать вам швидке завантаження із найближчого до вас регіону.[CR]  Всі додатки в цьому Репозиторії пройшли лише базове тестування. Якщо ви знайшли зламаний або непрацюючий додаток, будь-ласка повідомте про це Команду Kodi щоб ми могли вжити потрібних заходів.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Tải về và cài đặt add-on từ kho addon chính thức của Kodi.[CR]  Khi sử dụng kho chứa này bạn sẽ hưởng lợi từ dịch vụ tạo nguồn của chúng tôi, giúp bạn có thể tải về nhanh hơn từ vùng địa lý gần bạn.[CR]  Tất cả addon trên kho chứa này đã được thông qua bài kiểm tra cơ bản, nếu bạn phát hiện ra một addon không hoạt động xin vui lòng báo cáo lại nó cho đội ngũ Kodi để chúng tôi có thể kịp thời xử lý.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">从官方 Kodi.tv 插件库下载和安装插件。[CR]　通过官方插件库你将能利用我们广泛的镜像服务优势，使你能够就近下载资源。[CR]　官方库中的所有插件都经过了基本的测试，如果你发现有损坏或不能正常工作的插件请向 Kodi 开发团队报告，以便及时处理。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">從 Kodi.tv 官方的附加元件庫下載並安裝附加元件。[CR] 使用官方的附加元件庫你可以從離你較近的檔案鏡像伺器以較快的速度下載附加元件。[CR] 在這個附加元件庫中的附加元件都經過簡單的測試，如果你發現損壞或無法正常工作的附加元件，請回報給 Kodi 團隊，以讓 Kodi 團隊能做一些必須的處置。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Die Kodi span het nie al die byvoegsels in die kodebank gemaak nie en is nie verantwoordelik vir hulle inhoud nie</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="am_ET">የ Kodi ቡድን እዚህ ማጠራቀሚያ ውስጥ ያሉትን የ ተጨማ-ሪዎች ይዞታ አልፈጠሩም ስለዚህም ምንም አይነት ሀላፊነት አይወስዱም</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_SA">فريق Kodi لم يقم بصنع جميع اﻹضافات فى هذا المستودع وغير مسؤول عن محتواها</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Каманда Kodi не распрацоўвае усё дадаткі ў гэтым рэпазітары і не нясе адказнасці за іх змесціва</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Екипът на Kodi не е автор на всички добавки в хранилището и не носи отговорност за съдържанието им.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">L'equip de Kodi no ha fet tots els complements d'aquest dipòsit i per tant no són responsables del seu contingut.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Tým Kodi nevytvořil všechny doplňky v tomto repozitáři a není zodpovědný za jejich obsah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Nid Team Kodi wnaeth yr holl ychwanegion yn y storfa hon ac nid ydynt yn gyfrifol am eu cynnwys.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Team Kodi har ikke lavet alle add-ons i dette fjernlager og er ikke ansvarlig for deres indhold</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Die Addons in diesem Verzeichnis wurden nicht alle vom Team Kodi erstellt. Verantwortlich für den Inhalt sind die jeweiligen Autoren.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Η Ομάδα Kodi δεν δημιούργησε όλα τα πρόσθετα σε αυτό το αποθετήριο συνεπώς δεν είναι υπεύθυνη για το περιεχόμενό τους</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_AU">Team Kodi did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Team Kodi did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Team Kodi did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Team Kodi did not make all the add-ons on this repository and are not responsible for their content</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">No todos los add-ons en este repositorio han sido creados por el equipo de Kodi y este no es responsable de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">El equipo de Kodi no ha hecho todos los Add-ons de este repositorio y no son responsables de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">El equipo de Kodi no hizo todos los add-ons en este repositorio y no es responsable de su contenido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="et_EE">Kodi meeskond ei teinud kõiki lisasid selles hoidlas ja ei vastuta ka nende sisu eest.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Kodi taldeak ez ditu biltegi honetako gehigarri guztiak sortu eta ez da beren edukien erantzule.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fa_IR">همه افزونه های این منبع محصول کار تیم کودی نیستند و این تیم مسئولیتی در قبال محتوای آنها ندارد.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Team Kodi ei ole tehnyt kaikkia tässä ohjelmavarastossa olevia lisäosia, eikä siten ole vastuullinen kyseisten lisäosien sisällöstä</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">L’équipe Kodi n’a pas créé tous les addiciels de ce dépôt et n’est pas responsable de leur contenu</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">L’Équipe Kodi n’a pas créé toutes les extensions de ce dépôt et n’est pas responsable de leur contenu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">O equipo de Kodi non creou todos os Engadidos deste repositorio e non é responsábel do seu contido</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">צוות הפיתוח של Kodi לא יצר את כל ההרחבות שבמאגר זה ואיננו אחראי על תוכנן</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Kodi tim nije autor svih dodataka u ovom repozitoriju te kao takvi ne odgovaraju za njihov sadržaj</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Nem minden itt található kiegészítőt az Kodi csapat készített és nem vállal felelősséget azok tartalmáért</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Tim Kodi tidak membuat semua pengaya pada repository ini dan tidak bertanggung jawab atas isinya.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Kodi-teymið framleiðir ekki allar þessar viðbætur og er ekki ábyrgt fyrir innihaldi þeirra.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Il team di Kodi non ha creato tutti gli add-on di questa libreria e non è responsabile per il loro contenuto</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">Kodi チームが、このリポジトリ上の全アドオンを作ったわけではありません。また、その内容についても責任は負いかねます。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Team Kodi가 이 저장소의 모든 애드온을 제작한 것은 아니며, 애드온 컨텐츠에 대한 책임이 없습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Kodi komanda netestavo priedų šioje saugykloje ir neatsako arba nėra atsakinga už jų turinį</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lv_LV">Kodi komanda nav izveidojusi visus šīs krātuves pielikumus un nav atbildīga par to saturu</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="mk_MK">Kodi тимот ги нема направено сите овие додатоци и не е одговорен за нивната содржина</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Team Kodi tidak menghasilkan semua tambahan di dalam repositori ini dan tidak bertanggungjawab keatas kandungannya</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="mt_MT">Team Kodi m'għamilx l-add-ons kollha li hawn f'dan ir-repożitorju u mhumiex responsabbli għall-kontenut tagħhom</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Team Kodi har ikke utviklet alle utvidelsene i denne pakkebrønnen og er ikke ansvarlig for deres innhold</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Team Kodi heeft niet alle add-ons in deze depot geschreven en is niet verantwoordelijk voor hun inhoud.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Zespół Kodi nie tworzy wszystkich dodatków i nie bierze odpowiedzialności za ich zawartość</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">O Time do Kodi não produziu todos os add-ons deste repositório, e portanto não é responsável ​​por seu conteúdo</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">A Team Kodi não desenvolveu todos os add-ons neste repositório, e não é responsável pelo seu conteúdo.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Echipa Kodi nu a creat toate aceste suplimente din acest depozit și nu este responsabilă pentru conținutul lor.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Разработчики Kodi не являются авторами всех дополнений в данном репозитории и не несут ответственность за их содержимое.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Tým Kodi nevytvoril všetky doplnky v tomto zdroji nie je zodpovedný za ich obsah</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sl_SI">Ekipa Kodi ni naredila vseh dodatkov v tem skladišču in ne odgovarja za njihovo vsebino</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Тим Kodi није направио све додатке у овом спремишту и није одговоран за њихов садржај</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Tim-Kodi nije napravio sve dodatne programe u ovom spremištu i nije odgovoran za njihov sadržaj</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Team Kodi har inte gjort alla tillägg i förrådet och är inte ansvariga för innehållet i dessa.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Ekipa Kodi niy rychtuje wszyjskich przidŏwkōw i niy ôdpadŏ za jejich zawartość</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tg_TJ">Гурӯҳи кории Kodi дар ин анбори нармафзор соҳиби ҳамаи барномаҳои иловагӣ намебошад ва барои мӯҳтавояшон ҷавобгар намебшад</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">ทีม Kodi ไม่ได้จัดทำ ส่วนเสริม ทั้งหมดในแหล่งข้อมูลโปรแกรมนี้ และจะไม่รับผิดชอบต่อเนื้อหาเหล่านั้น</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Kodi takımı bu depodaki tüm eklentileri geliştirmemiştir ve bunların içeriklerinden sorumlu değildir.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Зауважте, що не всі додатки в цьому Репозиторії створені Командою Kodi, і тому Команда не несе відповідальності за їх вміст.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Đội ngũ Kodi không làm ra tất cả các add-on có trên kho chứa này và sẽ không chịu trách nhiệm về nội dung của các add-on đấy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">本库中插件不完全由 Kodi 团队开发，Kodi 团队对他人提交的内容不承担责任</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">這個附加元件庫的附加元件並非全部由 Kodi 團隊製作的，所以我們不對這些內容負責。</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.amazon-test"
       name="Amazon VOD"
       version="0.9.5"
       provider-name="Sandmann79, Varstahl">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.6.2"/>
    <import addon="script.module.mechanicalsoup" version="0.12.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.1.7"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.4.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.0.5"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyautogui" version="0.9.49"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
             library="default.py">
	<provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Amazon Prime Video Streaming</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Amazon Prime Instant Video</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Vídeo a demanda de Amazon Prime</summary>
    <summary lang="ua_UA">Потокове відео Amazon Prime</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Movies and Television Shows for Prime Members</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Filme und Serien für Amazon Prime Mitglieder</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Películas y Series para Miembros de Amazon Prime</description>
    <description lang="ua_UA">Фільми та серіали для підписників Prime</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Some parts of this addon may not be legal in your country of residence - please check with your local laws before installing.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Möglicherweise sind einge Teile dieses Addons in Ihrem Land illegal, Sie sollten dies unbedingt vor der Installation überprüfen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Algunas partes de este addon pueden que sean illegales en tu país de residencia - por favor, compruébalo antes de la instalación.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ua_UA">Деякі частини цього плагіну можуть бути незаконні в країні вашого проживання - будь ласка, перевірте це перед встановленням.</disclaimer>
    <forum>http://www.kodinerds.net/index.php/Thread/44211-Release-Amazon-Prime-Instant-Video</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/Sandmann79/xbmc</source>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
      <clearlogo>clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.tvheadend43" name="Tvheadend Server 4.3" version="10.0.111" provider-name="masQelec">
  <requires><import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>

  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="download.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Tvheadend: a TV streaming server for Linux</summary>
    <description lang="en">Tvheadend (ca756e3): is a TV streaming server for Linux supporting DVB-S/S2, DVB-C, DVB-T/T2, IPTV, SAT>IP, ATSC and ISDB-T</description>
    <summary lang="es">Tvheadend: un servidor de transmisión de TV para Linux</summary>
    <description lang="es">Tvheadend (ca756e3): es un servidor de transmisión de TV para Linux compatible DVB-S/S2, DVB-C, DVB-T/T2, IPTV, SAT>IP, ATSC y ISDB-T</description>
    <disclaimer></disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
104
- tvh bump to c66e3bc (master 2020.10.22)

103
- tvh bump to 0f13f59 (master 2020.07.07)

102
- tvh bump to 51a4c5b (master 2020.06.10)

101
- python3, tvh bump to 2af3b9e (master 2020.05.22)
- update gnutls to 3.6.14

100
- initial CoreELEC version
    </news>
    <assets><icon>resources/icon.png</icon><fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.png</screenshot>

    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.routing" name="Plugin routing" version="0.2.3" provider-name="takoi">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Routing module for plugins</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Library for building and parsing plugin URLs.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Módulo de enrutamiento para complementos</summary>
        <description lang="es_ES">Biblioteca para construir y analizar URL de complementos.</description>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <language>en_GB</language>
        <source>https://github.com/tamland/kodi-plugin-routing</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.webinterface" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="1.0.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="webinterface" schema="webinterface.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.dateutil"
       name="python-dateutil"
       version="2.8.1"
       provider-name="Paul Ganssle, Gustavo Niemeyer">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.5"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Extensions to the standard Python datetime module</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The dateutil module provides powerful extensions to the standard datetime module, available in Python.</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Extensiones al módulo estándar de fecha y hora de Python</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">El módulo dateutil proporciona extensiones potentes al módulo estándar de fecha y hora, disponible en Python.</description>
    <license>Apache-2.0, BSD-3-Clause</license>
    <website>https://dateutil.readthedocs.io/en/stable/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/dateutil/dateutil</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="0.1"/>
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
</addon>

<addon id="service.cloud.masqelec" name="Cloud masQelec" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Cloud masQelec">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="autoexec.py">
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="es_ES">Cloud masQelec mantiene actualizada tu biblioteca.</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Cloud masQelec mantiene actualizada tu biblioteca.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<assets>
      			<icon>icon.png</icon>
   		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.disney.plus" name="Disney+" provider-name="Slyguy" version="0.12.4">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.slyguy"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" provides="video">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Disney+ is the exclusive home for your favorite movies and TV shows from Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars, and National Geographic.

Subscription required.</description>
    <description lang="it">Disney+ è la casa esclusiva per i tuoi film e programmi TV preferiti di Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars e National Geographic.

Abbonamento richiesto.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Disney+ est la destination exclusive de vos films et séries TV préférés des univers Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars et National Geographic.

Abonnement requis.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Disney+ je exkluzivní místo pro vaše oblíbené filmy a televizní pořady ze světa Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars a National Geographic.

Je nutné předplatné.</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Add Czech translation. Thanks Ludek</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplecache" name="Simple Cache Module" version="1.0.18" provider-name="marcelveldt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</description>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Proporciona una memoria caché simple basada en archivos y memoria para complementos de Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="es_ES">Proporciona una memoria caché simple basada en archivos y memoria para complementos de Kodi</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <forum/>
        <source>https://github.com/kodi-community-addons/script.module.simplecache</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.addon.signals"
    name="Addon Signals"
    version="0.0.6"
    provider-name="Rick Phillips (ruuk)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Inter-addon signalling</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Inter-addon señalización</summary>
		<description lang="en">Provides signal/slot mechanism for inter-addon communication</description>
		<description lang="es">Proporciona un mecanismo de signal/slot para la comunicación entre complementos</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>LGPL-2.1-only</license>
        <source>https://github.com/ruuk/script.module.addon.signals</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.soupsieve" name="Soup Sieve" version="1.9.6" provider-name="Isaac Muse">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">A CSS selector library</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Soup Sieve is a CSS selector library designed to be used with Beautiful Soup 4. It aims to provide selecting, matching, and filtering using modern CSS selectors.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Una biblioteca de selectores de CSS</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Soup Sieve es una biblioteca de selectores CSS diseñada para ser utilizada con Beautiful Soup 4. Su objetivo es proporcionar selección, emparejamiento y filtrado utilizando selectores CSS modernos.</description>
		<license>MIT</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/soupsieve/</website>
		<source>https://github.com/facelessuser/soupsieve</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="resource.language.es_es"
  version="9.0.23"
  name="Spanish"
  provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="kodi.resource.language"
    locale="es_ES">
    <charsets>
      <gui>CP1252</gui>
      <subtitle>CP1252</subtitle>
    </charsets>
    <sorttokens>
      <token>The</token>
      <token>El</token>
      <token>Los</token>
      <token>La</token>
      <token>Las</token>
      <token>Un</token>
    </sorttokens>
  </extension>
  <extension point="kodi.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Spanish language pack</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Paquete de idioma español</summary>
    <description lang="en">Spanish version of all texts used in Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es">Versión en español de todos los textos utilizados en Kodi.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.globalsearch" name="Global Search" version="8.0.13" provider-name="ronie">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Търси в библиотеката Ви.</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Cerca a la teva biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Hledej v knihovně</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Durchsuchen Sie Ihre Bibliothek.</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Αναζήτηση στη Συλλογή σας.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Busca tu biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Chercher dans la médiathèque.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Chercher dans votre bibliothèque</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Buscar a súa biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">חיפוש בספריית המדיה.</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Pretražite svoju zbirku.</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Keresés a médiatárban</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Cari pustaka Anda.</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Ricerca nella la tua libreria.</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">라이브러리 찾기</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Ieškoti bibliotekoje.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Zoek in je bibliotheek.</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Søk i biblioteket ditt</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Przeszukaj swoją bibliotekę</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Faça buscas na sua biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Pesquise sua coleção.</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Căutați în mediateca dumneavoastră.</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Поиск в вашей медиатеке.</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Iščite v svoji knjižnici.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Sök i ditt bibliotek.</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Kitaplığını ara</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">资料库搜索</summary>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Добавката може да намери всеки елемент във вашата видео и музикална библиотека.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Aquest complement pot trobat qualsevol article en la teva biblioteca de vídeo i música</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Tento dopněk dokáže najít libovolnou položku ve vaší audio a video knihovně.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Dieses Add-on kann jeden Eintrag in Ihrer Video- und Musikbibliothek finden.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Αυτό το πρόσθετο μπορεί να βρει κάθε αντικείμενο στις συλλογές σας.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Este complemento puede encontrar cualquier elemento en tu biblioteca de vídeo y música.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Cette extension peut trouver tout élément dans la vidéothèque et l'audiothèque.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Cet addiciel peut trouver tout élément dans votre vidéothèque et dans votre audiothèque.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Este complemento pode atopar calquera elemento na súa biblioteca de medios.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">הרחבה זו יכולה למצוא כל פריט בספריות הווידאו והמוזיקה.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Ovaj dodatak može pronaći svaku stavku u vašoj videoteci ili fonoteci.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Ez a kiegészítő bármely elemet megtalálja a videó és audió médiatárban.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Addon ini dapat mencari item apa saja di pustaka video dan musik Anda.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Questo addon può trovare ogni elemento nella tua libreria video ed in quella musicale.</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">비디오와 음악 라이브러리의 모든 항목을 검색합니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Šis priedas gali rasti bet kokį elementą jūsų vaizdo ir garso bibliotekoje.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Deze addon kan elk item in je video- en muziekbibliotheken vinden.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Dette tillegget kan finne hva som helst i ditt film eller musikk bibliotek.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Ten plugin może odnaleźć dowolną pozycję w twojej bibliotece wideo oraz muzycznej.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Este addon pode encontrar qualquer item na sua biblioteca de vídeos e de músicas.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Este addon pode encontrar qualquer item na sua coleção de vídeos e música.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Acest supliment poate găsi orice element în mediateca dumneavoastră video și audio.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Это дополнение поможет найти любую запись в вашей медиатеке.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Ta dodatek lahko poišče katerokoli podatek v vaši knjižnici filmov in glasbe.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Detta tillägg kan hitta vilket objekt som helst i ditt video och musikbibliotek.</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Bu eklenti video ve müzik kitaplığınızdaki herhangi bir öğeyi bulabilir.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">此插件搜索你的视频和音乐资料库项目。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=109301</forum>
		<source>https://gitlab.com/ronie/script.globalsearch/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>- fix issue with unneeded seeking</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.hbogoeu" name="hGO EU" provider-name="arvvoid" version="2.7.9">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4" />
    <import addon="script.module.pyaes" version="1.6.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.defusedxml" version="0.6.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.5.2" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="main.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Watch HBO® GO EU+Nordic content in Kodi. Valid HBO® account required.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">
The add-on has reached end of life. The Hbo Go service has been replaced by Hbo Max in all regions supported by this add-on. Search the Kodi forums for the Hbo Max add-on.


Simple, Kodi add-on to access HBO® Go EU content. (This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®.)

Important, HBO® Go must be paid for!!!  You need a valid account!
Register on the official HBO® Go website for your region.

Read the disclaimer!

Curently support: Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Czech Republic, Hungary, Macedonia, Montenegro, Polonia, Portugal, Romania, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenija, Spain, Norway, Denmark, Sweden, Finland

To report bugs or request assistence with the add-on go to: https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu
    </description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®. The trademark HBO® Go is registered by Home Box Office, Inc.
For more information on HBO® Go visit the official HBO® Go website for your region.
I do not own any of the content this add-on lists. The content belongs to Home Box Office, Inc.
All this add-on does is make simple HTTP requests to Hbo go servers to retrieve and display content just like any web browser would do!

Important: HBO® Go must be paid for!!! You need a valid HBO® Go account for the add-on to work! Register on the official HBO® Go website for your region

THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE ADD-ON, IT MIGHT NOT WORK AT ALL AND IT CAN BREAK AND STOP WORKING AT ANY TIME.

If an official app is available for your platform, use it instead of this.
    </disclaimer>
    <language>en bs bg hr cs hu mk pl pt ro sr sk sl es nb da sv fi cnr</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=339798</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu</source>
    <website>https://arvvoid.github.io/plugin.video.hbogoeu</website>
    <news>
- Add-on end of life
    </news>
    <broken>The add-on has reached end of life. The Hbo Go service has been replaced by Hbo Max in all regions supported by this add-on. Search the Kodi forums for the Hbo Max add-on.</broken>
    <assets>
     <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
     <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
     <screenshot>resources/screen1.jpg</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen2.jpg</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen3.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.youtube" name="YouTube" version="7.0.2.1" provider-name="anxdpanic, bromix">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
        <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="20.3.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.2.2" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="script.module.infotagger" version="0.0.5"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/startup.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <news>
[new] quality and stream feature selection
[new] enable HLS live streams
[new] stream and language labelling
[chg] separately enable local/remote history
[chg] restore unsupported compatibility for Kodi v19 (Matrix)
[fix] fix various playback issues |contrib: various|
[fix] Limit host connections getting subscription feeds |contrib: cas--|
[fix] fix handling of connection failures
[upd] Translations updated from Kodi Weblate
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://ytaddon.panicked.xyz/forum</forum>
        <website>https://www.youtube.com</website>
        <source>https://github.com/anxdpanic/plugin.video.youtube</source>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="bg_BG">Добавка за YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Plugin pro YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Plugin til YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Plugin für YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Plugin for YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Plugin para YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="es_MX">Complemento para YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">YouTube-lisäosa</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Plugin pour YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="he_IL">תוסף עבור YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Dodatak za YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="hu_HU">YouTube kiegészítő</summary>
        <summary lang="id_ID">Pengaya untuk YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Plugin per YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="ko_KR">유튜브 플러그인</summary>
        <summary lang="nb_NO">Tillegg for YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Plugin voor YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Видеодополнение YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="sk_SK">Doplnok pre YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="tr_TR">YouTube için eklenti</summary>
        <summary lang="vi_VN">Plugin dành cho YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">油管插件</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_TW">YouTube附加元件</summary>
        <description lang="bg_BG">YouTube е един от най-големите уеб сайтове за споделяне на видео в целия свят.</description>
        <description lang="cs_CZ">YouTube je jedna z největších webových stránek světa sdílející video.</description>
        <description lang="da_DK">YouTube er et af verdens største videodelingswebsteder.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">YouTube ist eines der größten Video-Sharing-Websites der Welt.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το YouTube είναι μία από τις μεγαλύτερες ιστοσελίδες διαμοιρασμού βίντεο στον κόσμο.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">YouTube is one of the biggest video-sharing websites of the world.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">YouTube es uno de los sitios web más grande del mundo para compartir vídeos.</description>
        <description lang="es_MX">YouTube es uno de los más grandes sitios web de intercambio de videos del mundo.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">YouTube on yksi maailman suurimmista videoiden jakosivustoista.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">YouTube est l&amp;apos;un des plus grands sites de partage vidéos du monde.</description>
        <description lang="he_IL">YouTube הוא אחד מאתרי שיתוף הווידאו הגדולים בעולם.</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">YouTube je jedna od najvećih stranica za dijeljenje video sadržaja na svijetu.</description>
        <description lang="hu_HU">A YouTube világ egyik legnagyobb videómegosztó weboldala.</description>
        <description lang="id_ID">YouTube adalah salah satu situs web berbagi video terbesar di dunia.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">YouTube è uno dei più grandi siti di condivisione video del mondo.</description>
        <description lang="ko_KR">유튜브는 세상에서 가장 큰 동영상 공유 사이트 중의 하나입니다.</description>
        <description lang="nb_NO">YouTube er en av verdens største nettsider for videodeling.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">YouTube is een van de grootste videodelenwebsite in de hele wereld.</description>
        <description lang="pl_PL">YouTube jest jednym z największych na świecie serwisów udostępniania wideo.</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">YouTube - популярнейший видеохостинговый сайт, предоставляющий пользователям услуги хранения, доставки и показа видео.</description>
        <description lang="sk_SK">YouTube je jednou z najväčších stránok na zdieľanie videa na svete.</description>
        <description lang="tr_TR">YouTube, dünya üzerindeki en büyük video paylaşma platformlarından birisidir.</description>
        <description lang="vi_VN">YouTube là một trong những trang web chia sẻ video lớn nhất trên thế giới.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">油管是世界上最大的视频分享网站之一。</description>
        <description lang="zh_TW">Youtube 是全世界最大的影片分享網站。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Tento plugin není schválen společností Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="da_DK">Dette plugin er ikke godkendt af Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Dieses Plugin ist nicht von Google befürwortet</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Η παρούσα μικροεφαρμογή δεν έχει υϊοθετηθεί από την Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This plugin is not endorsed by Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Este add-on no está respaldado por Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Este complemento no está respaldado por Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Google ei tue tätä lisäosaa</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Ce module n&amp;apos;est pas validé par Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Ovaj dodatak nije podržan od strane Googlea</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="id_ID">Plugin ini tidak didukung oleh Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it_IT">Questo plugin non è approvato da Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko_KR">이 플러그인은 Google의 허가를 받지 않았습니다</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Deze plug-in wordt niet door Google ondersteund</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Ta wtyczka nie jest zatwierdzona przez Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Плагин не поддерживается Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Tento doplnok nie je schválený spoločnosťou Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Bu eklenti Google tarafından üretilmemiştir</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="vi_VN">Plugin này không được xác nhận bởi Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">此插件未被谷歌认可</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">此附加元件未由Google支持</disclaimer>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="weather.gismeteo" version="0.6.3" name="Gismeteo" provider-name="vl.maksime">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simpleplugin3" version="3.0.5"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.15.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.weather" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Gismeteo Weather Forecast. Real time weather and detailed forecast all round the world</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Прогноз погоды от ведущего погодного сервиса Gismeteo</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Pronóstico del tiempo Gismeteo. Clima en tiempo real y pronóstico detallado en todo el mundo</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Gismeteo prévisions météorologiques. Prévisions météorologiques en temps réel à travers le monde.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Gismeteo Weather Forecast. Realtidsväder och detaljerade prognoser över hela världen</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Gismeteo veðurspá. Rauntíma veðurlýsing og nákvæmar veðurspár um víða veröld</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">The weather is provided solely for personal non-commercial use</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Погода предоставлена исключительно для личного некоммерческого использования</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">El clima se proporciona únicamente para su uso personal y no comercial</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">La météo est fournie pour un usage personnel non-commercial.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Vädret tillhandahålls enbart för personligt, icke-kommersiellt bruk</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Veðurupplýsingarnar eru einungis til einkanota og ekki í hagnaðarskyni</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The weather forecast has been prepared by MapMakers Group Ltd</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Прогноз погоды подготовлен НПЦ "Мэп Мейкер"</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">El pronóstico del tiempo ha sido preparado por MapMakers Group Ltd</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Les prévisions météorologiques sont mises à disposition par MapMakers Group Ltd</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Väderprognosen har utarbetats av MapMakers Group Ltd.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Veðurspáin var útbúin af MapMakers Group Ltd</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=323624</forum>
		<website>https://www.gismeteo.com/</website>
		<email>vl.maksime@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/vlmaksime/weather.gismeteo</source>
		<news>v0.6.3 (2021-09-27)[CR]- Fixed identified bugs[CR][CR]v0.6.2 (2021-05-31)[CR]- Updated compatibility with Kodi 19[CR]- Added Icelandic translation (sveinki) [CR][CR]v0.6.1 (2021-04-03)[CR]- SimplePlugin 3 module moved into external addon[CR]- Small changes in the add-on structure [CR]- Added French translation (DavidHenryThoreau)[CR]- Added Swedish translation (Sopor)</news>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache"
       name="backports.functools_lru_cache"
       version="1.6.1"
       provider-name="Jason R. Coombs">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Backport of functools.lru_cache from Python 3.3</summary>
    <description lang="en">Packed for Kodi from https://github.com/jaraco/backports.functools_lru_cache</description>
    <summary lang="es">Backport de functools.lru_cache de Python 3.3</summary>
    <description lang="es">Empaquetado para Kodi de https://github.com/jaraco/backports.functools_lru_cache</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/jaraco/backports.functools_lru_cache</website>
    <source>https://github.com/Razzeee/script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyaes"
    name="PyAES"
    version="1.6.1"
    provider-name="ricmoo">

    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Pure-Python Implementation of the AES block-cipher and common modes of operation</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A pure-Python implementation of the AES (FIPS-197) block-cipher algorithm and common modes of operation (CBC, CFB, CTR, ECB, OFB) with no dependencies beyond standard Python libraries. See README.md for API reference and details.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Implementación de Pure-Python del cifrado de bloque AES y modos comunes de operación</summary>
        <description lang="es_ES">Una implementación de Python puro del algoritmo de cifrado de bloques AES (FIPS-197) y modos comunes de operación (CBC, CFB, CTR, ECB, OFB) sin dependencias más allá de las bibliotecas estándar de Python. Ver README.md para referencia de API y detalles.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <website>https://github.com/ricmoo/pyaes</website>
        <source>https://github.com/ricmoo/pyaes</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <backwards-compatibility abi="1.0"/>
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.core" version="0.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension-point id="scraper.albums" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.artists" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.movies" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.musicvideos" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.tvshows" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
  <extension-point id="scraper.library" schema="scraper.xsd"/>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.balandro" name="[COLOR aqua]Balandro[/COLOR] Repo" version="4.0.0" provider-name="Team Balandro">

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="balandro repo">
        <dir>
            <info>https://pastebin.com/raw/Lktm2YS0</info>
            <checksum>https://pastebin.com/raw/asquZ060</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/repobal/base/main/</datadir>
        </dir>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
       <summary>Repositorio de Balandro</summary>
       <assets>
          <icon>icon.png</icon>
       </assets>
       <news>
       [COLOR darkorange][B]Versión  [/COLOR][COLOR yellow]4.0.0[/COLOR][COLOR red]  Enero 2024[/B][/COLOR]

       [COLOR goldenrod][B]Media Centers:[/B][/COLOR]
           [COLOR tan][B]Kodi Versiones Oficiales Soportadas:[/B][/COLOR]
           [COLOR plum][B]21.x Omega,  20.x Nexus,  19.x Matrix,[/B][/COLOR]
           [COLOR plum][B]18.x Leia  y  17.x Krypton[/B][/COLOR]

       [COLOR springgreen][B]Fuente[/COLOR]  [COLOR cyan]repobal.github.io/base/[/B][/COLOR]
       </news>
       <summary>Balandro es un Navegador de Páginas Webs</summary>
       <description>[COLOR moccasin][B]Navega con Kodi por Páginas Webs para poder ver sus contenidos de manera fácil. [COLOR yellow]Balandro es desde el año [COLOR cyan]2018[COLOR yellow] un MOD derivado de [COLOR yellowgreen]Pelisalacarta y Alfa[COLOR yellow],[COLOR mediumaquamarine] y tiene como objeto, permitir visualizar [COLOR deepskyblue]Películas[COLOR mediumaquamarine], [COLOR hotpink]Series[COLOR mediumaquamarine], [COLOR darkcyan]Documentales[COLOR mediumaquamarine], etc., todo a través de Internet y directamente desde su sistema Media Center. [COLOR orchid]Este Add-On es tan solo un mero Ejercicio de Aprendizaje del Lenguaje de Programación Python y se distribuye sin Ningún Contenido Multimedia adjunto al mismo [COLOR lightgrey][I]En consecuencia solo las Webs son Plenamente Responsables de los contenidos que publiquen.[/I][/B][/COLOR]</description>
       <disclaimer>[COLOR aqua][B]Los Propietarios y Distribuidores de este Add-On no Proveen ni Distribuyen Ningún Contenido Mostrado por el Add-On, ni Tienen Afiliación alguna con los Proveedores/Webs de contenidos. [COLOR tan]Está Prohibida su distribución, solo ó junto con Contenidos Multimedia Protegidos por los Derechos de Autor. [COLOR chocolate]Si este tipo de contenido está Prohibido en su País, solamente Usted será el Responsable de su uso. [COLOR white]La vulneración de estas prohibiciones Exonerarán de cualquier Culpa a sus Autores, [COLOR red]Siendo el unico Responsable quien lo haya Distribuido ó Utilizado Ilegalmente.[/B][/COLOR]</disclaimer>
       <platform>all</platform>
       <license>GNU GPL v3</license>
       <source>https://repobal.github.io/base/</source>
       <forum>https://www.mimediacenter.info/foro/</forum>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login|startup" />
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.unidecode" name="unidecode" version="1.1.1" provider-name="Tomaz Solc (Tomaz.solc@tablix.org)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en">ASCII transliterations of Unicode text by Sean M. Burke and Tomaz Solc</summary>
		<description lang="en">ASCII transliterations of Unicode text by Sean M. Burke and Tomaz Solc</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Code taken from https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">Transliteraciones ASCII de texto Unicode por Sean M. Burke y Tomaz Solc</summary>
		<description lang="es">Transliteraciones ASCII de texto Unicode por Sean M. Burke y Tomaz Solc</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Código tomado de https://pypi.python.org/pypi/Unidecode</disclaimer>
		<license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</website>
		<source>https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pycryptodome"
       name="Python Crypto Library"
       version="3.4.3"
       provider-name="Legrandin">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.7.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="resource.language.en_gb"
  version="2.0.1"
  name="English"
  provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="kodi.resource.language"
    locale="en_GB">
    <charsets>
      <gui>CP1252</gui>
      <subtitle>CP1252</subtitle>
    </charsets>
    <sorttokens>
      <token>The</token>
    </sorttokens>
  </extension>
  <extension point="kodi.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">English language pack</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Paquete de idioma Ingles</summary>
    <description lang="en">English version of all texts used in Kodi.</description>
	<description lang="es">Versión en Ingles de todos los textos utilizados en Kodi.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en">English is the default language for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
	<disclaimer lang="es">El inglés es el idioma predeterminado para Kodi, eliminarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.clouddrive.common" name="Cloud Drive Common Module" version="1.2.12" provider-name="Carlos Guzman (cguZZman)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.dateutil"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pyqrcode"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="/" />
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Cloud Drive Common Module</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Common Services and Classes for all the cloud drive addons.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Módulo Común Cloud Drive</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Servicios comunes y clases para todos los complementos de unidades en la nube.</description>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מודול משותף לכונן בענן</summary>
		<description lang="he_IL">שירותים ושירותים משותפים לכל התוספים של כונן הענן.</description>
		<license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
		<source>https://github.com/cguZZman/script.module.clouddrive.common</source>
		<forum>https://github.com/cguZZman/script.module.clouddrive.common/issues</forum>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
		<news>
v1.2.12 released Mar 3, 2020:
- NFO export
		</news>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This cloud drive addon uses a third-party authentication mechanism commonly known as OAuth 2.0.
If you want to know more about OAuth 2.0 you can visit the following pages:
- https://oauth.net/2/
- https://developers.google.com/identity/protocols/OAuth2
- https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/onedrive/developer/rest-api/getting-started/msa-oauth

Kodi and myself take no responsibility or liability whatsoever.

The authentication server URL is specified in Settings / Advanced / Sign-in Server. The Sign-in Server implements the OAuth 2.0 protocol.
The complete source code of the Sign-in Server can be download here: https://github.com/cguZZman/drive-login
You can clone the project and host it in your own server.
		</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">
Este complemento de unidad en la nube utiliza un mecanismo de autenticación de terceros comúnmente conocido como OAuth 2.0.
Si desea saber más sobre OAuth 2.0, puede visitar las siguientes páginas:
- https://oauth.net/2/
- https://developers.google.com/identity/protocols/OAuth2
- https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/onedrive/developer/rest-api/getting-started/msa-oauth

Kodi y yo no asumimos responsabilidad alguna.

La URL del servidor de autenticación se especifica en Configuración / Avanzado / Servidor de inicio de sesión. El servidor de inicio de sesión implementa el protocolo OAuth 2.0.
El código fuente completo del servidor de inicio de sesión se puede descargar aquí: https://github.com/cguZZman/drive-login
Puede clonar el proyecto y alojarlo en su propio servidor.
		</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyxbmct"
   name="PyXBMCt"
   version="1.3.1"
   provider-name="Roman V.M.">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" />
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">PyXBMCt UI framework</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">PyXBMCt is a mini-framework for simple XBMC addon UI buliding. It is similar to PyQt and provides parent windows, a number of UI controls (widgets) and a grid layout manager to place controls.</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">PyXBMCt UI framework</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">PyXBMCt es un mini-framework para un simple complemento de UI del complemento XBMC. Es similar a PyQt y proporciona ventanas principales, una serie de controles de interfaz de usuario (widgets) y un administrador de diseño de cuadrícula para colocar controles.</description>
    <license>GNU GPL v.3</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=174859</forum>
    <website>http://romanvm.github.io/script.module.pyxbmct/</website>
    <email>roman1972@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/romanvm/script.module.pyxbmct</source>
    <news>1.3.1:
- Fix incompatibility with newer Python 3 Kodi builds
- Replace future library with six for Python 3 compatibility</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.six"
       name="six"
       version="1.15.0"
       provider-name="gutworth">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
    		version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python 2 and 3 compatibility utilities.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Six is a Python 2 and 3 compatibility library. It provides utility functions for smoothing over the differences between the Python versions with the goal of writing Python code that is compatible on both Python versions. See the documentation for more information on what is provided.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/benjaminp/six</source>
    <website>https://pypi.org/project/six/</website>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL" version="5.1.4" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" /> -->
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="0.0.1"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.cryptopy" version="1.2.6" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.gdrive" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup4" name="BeautifulSoup4" version="4.9.3" provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.soupsieve" version="1.9.6"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Screen-scraping library</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Beautiful Soup is a library that makes it easy to scrape information from web pages. It sits atop an HTML or XML parser, providing Pythonic idioms for iterating, searching, and modifying the parse tree.</description>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Biblioteca de screen-scraping</summary>
		<description lang="es_ES">Beautiful Soup es una biblioteca que facilita la extracción de información de páginas web. Se asienta sobre un analizador HTML o XML, proporcionando modismos Pythonic para iterar, buscar y modificar el árbol de análisis.</description>
		<license>MIT</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<website>https://www.crummy.com/software/BeautifulSoup/</website>
		<source>https://code.launchpad.net/beautifulsoup</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.elementum.burst" name="Elementum [COLOR FFFF6B00]Burst[/COLOR]" version="0.0.71" provider-name="elgatito">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.0.0" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.elementum" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.16.0.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="burst.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Elementum torrents provider</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Elementum torrent pružatelji usluga</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Proveedor de torrents Elementum</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Поисковое дополнение Elementum</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Elementum-torrentleverantör</summary>
        <description lang="en">Elementum Burst is a lean and mean multi-provider for Elementum.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Elementum Burst je višestruki pružatelj usluga za Elementum.</description>
        <description lang="es">Elementum Burst es un multi-proveedor simple y eficiente para Elementum.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Elementum Burst это поисковое дополнение, для поиска торрентов для Elementum.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Elementum Burst är en enkel och effektiv multi-leverantör för Elementum.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Autor ovog dodatka ne posjeduje i ne distribuira bilo kakav sadržaj koji je pronađen. Autor nije povezan sa bilo kojim izvorom sadržaja.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">El autor no aloja ni distribuye ninguno de los contenidos mostrados por este complemento. El autor no tiene ninguna afiliación con los proveedores de contenido.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Автор не несёт ответственности за использование дополнения, не распространяет данные, выводимые дополнением.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Skaparen är inte värd eller distribuerar något av innehållet som visas av detta tillägg. Skaparen har ingen anslutning till innehållsleverantörerna.</disclaimer>
        <license>WTFPL, Version 2, December 2004. See included LICENSE.</license>
        <website>https://elementum.surge.sh</website>
        <source>https://github.com/elgatito/script.elementum.burst</source>
        <forum>TODO</forum>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup"
       name="BeautifulSoup"
       version="3.2.1"
       provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
    		version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">HTML/XML parser for quick-turnaround applications like screen-scraping</summary>
    <description lang="en">Beautiful Soup parses arbitrarily invalid SGML and provides a variety of methods and Pythonic idioms for iterating and searching the parse tree.</description>
    <summary lang="es">Analizador HTML / XML para aplicaciones de respuesta rápida como el raspado de pantalla</summary>
    <description lang="es">Beautiful Soup analiza SGML arbitrariamente inválido y proporciona una variedad de métodos y expresiones idiomáticas pitónicas para iterar y buscar en el árbol de análisis.</description>
	<license>BSD</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.iagl" name="Internet Archive Game Launcher" version="2.1.6">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil"/>
    <import addon="script.module.elementtree"/>
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.routing"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube"/>
    <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>game</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <!-- <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker> -->
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) is a FREE Kodi addon that will browse and launch games available from the Internet</description>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="es_ES">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) es un complemento gratuito para Kodi que explora y lanza juegos disponibles en Internet</description>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="es_MX">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) es un complemento gratuito para Kodi que explorará y lanzará juegos disponibles en Internet</description>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) é um addon gratuito para Kodi que explora e executa jogos disponíveis na Internet</description>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Internet Archive Game Launcher</summary>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Internet Archive Game Launcher (IAGL) é um addon gratuito para Kodi que explora e executa jogos disponíveis na Internet</description>
    <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=231339</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/zach-morris/plugin.program.iagl</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen1.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen2.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen3.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen4.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen5.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>support/media/screen6.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.urllib3" name="urllib3" version="1.26.9" provider-name="urllib3">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">urllib3 is a powerful, user-friendly HTTP client for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">urllib3 is a powerful, user-friendly HTTP client for Python. Much of the Python ecosystem already uses urllib3 and you should too. urllib3 brings many critical features that are missing from the Python standard libraries</description>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>https://urllib3.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/urllib3/urllib3</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.elementtree"
       name="Elementtree XML parser"
       version="1.2.8"
       provider-name="http://effbot.org/zone/element-index.htm">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="slyguy.dependencies" name="SlyGuy Dependencies" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.0.5">
  <requires>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/modules" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Dependencies required by all Slyguy add-ons</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Bump requests > 2.27.1</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.mechanicalsoup"
	name="MechanicalSoup"
	version="1.0.0"
	provider-name="Matthew Hickford, Dan Hemberger, Matthieu Moy">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.4.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.six" version="1.4.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">A Python library for automating interaction with websites.</summary>
		<forum></forum>
		<website>https://mechanicalsoup.readthedocs.io/</website>
		<license>MIT</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<source>https://github.com/MechanicalSoup/MechanicalSoup</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.slyguy" name="SlyGuy Common" provider-name="SlyGuy" version="0.54.3">
  <requires>
    <import addon="slyguy.dependencies"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/modules" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description lang="en">Common code required by all Slyguy add-ons</description>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news>Allow !(not) operator for languages in addon settings</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.hdtrailers_net" name="HD-Trailers.net" version="1.2.2" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>http://www.hd-trailers.net</website>
    <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.video.hdtrailers_net</source>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=148400</forum>
    <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <summary lang="ar">مقاطع مرئيه من مصادر مختلفه بجوده عاليه الوضوح</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Trailer and Clips from several sources in HD</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Трейлъри и клипове от няколко източника в HD качество</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Tràiler i Fragments de Vídeo des de diferents fonts en HD</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Trailer og klip fra adskillige kilder i HD</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Trailer und Clips aus verschiedenen Quellen in HD</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Διαφημιστικά και Αποσπάσματα από διάφορες πηγές σε υψηλή ποιότητα (HD)</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Trailer and Clips from several sources in HD</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Trailer y Clips de varias fuentes en HD</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Bandes annonces et Clips provenant de plusieurs sources en HD</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Bandes-annonce et clips vidéos de diverse sources en haute définition</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Trailers e Clips de diferentes fontes en HD</summary>
    <summary lang="he">קדימונים וסרטונים ממספר מקורות באיכות HD</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Najave i video inserti iz nekoliko HD izvora</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Ajánlók és videóklipek számos forrásból HD minőségben</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Trailer e Filmati da svariate fonti in HD</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">다양한 출처의 HD 예고편과 비디오 클립</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Trailers en Clips van verschillende bronnen in HD</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Trailere og snutter fra flere kilder i HD</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Zwiastuny i klipy z kilku źródeł w HD</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Trailers e clipes de várias fontes em HD</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Trailers e Clipes de várias fontes em HD</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Ukážky a klipy z rôznych zdrojov v HD kvalite</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Trailers och klipp från flera olika källor i HD</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">多个来源的高清预告片和电影剪辑</summary>
    <description lang="ar">هذا الملحق يوفر بلوغاً سهلاً للأفلام القصيره ومقاطع اﻷفلام. وبالتحديد يمكنك بلوغها من خلال :[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]اغلب اﻷفلام القصيره متوفره بجوده 480 و 720 و 1080</description>
    <description lang="be">This Plugin provides access to Movie Trailers and Clips. You can download trailers and add movies to CouchPotato. It provides access to Trailers from:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Most of them are available in 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="bg">Добавката предоставя достъп до трейлъри и клипове на филми. Можете да сваляте трейлъри и да добавяте филми в CouchPotato. Предоставя достъп до трейлърите от: [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Повечето са налични в резолюция 480p, 720p и 1080p</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest complement permet l'accés a tràilers de pel·lícules i fragments de vídeo. Podeu descarregar tràilers i afegir pel·lícules a CouchPotato. Proporciona accés a Tràilers de:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La majoria d'ells estan disponibles a 480p, 720p i 1080p</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne Addon giver adgang til filmtrailere og klip fra de følgende kilder:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De fleste af dem er tilgængelige i 480p, 720p og 1080p</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieses Plugin bietet Zugriff auf verschiedene Film Trailer und Clips der folgenden Quellen:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Die meisten sind verfügbar in 480p, 720p und 1080p</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το Plugin σας παρέχει πρόσβαση σε Διαφημιστικά και Αποσπάσματα Ταινιών από τις ακόλουθες πηγές:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Τα περισσότερα από αυτά είναι διαθέσιμα σε ανάλυση 480p, 720p και 1080p</description>
    <description lang="en">This Plugin provides access to Movie Trailers and Clips. You can download trailers and add movies to CouchPotato. It provides access to Trailers from:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Most of them are available in 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="es">Este Plugin proporciona acceso a Trailers y Clips de películas. Puede descargar trailers y añadir películas a CouchPotato. Proporciona acceso a Trailer de: [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La mayoría de ellos están disponibles en 480p, 720p y 1080p</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce plugin donne accès aux Bande-annonces et Clips. Vous pouvez télécharger les bande-annonces et ajouter les films à CouchPotato. Cela donne accès aux Bande-annonces de :[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La plupart sont disponibles en 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Ce plugiciel permet d'accéder à des bandes-annonces et des clips. Vous pouvez télécharger des bandes-annonces et ajouter des films à Couchpotato. Il donne accès à des bandes-annonces provenant de : [CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]La plupart sont disponibles en 480p, 720p et 1080p.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este Engadido fornece de acceso a Trailers e Clips de filmes. Pode baixar trailers e engadir filmes a CouchPotato. Este fornece de acceso a Trailers de:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Moitos deles dispoñíbeis a 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
    <description lang="he">הרחבה זו מספקת גישה לקדימוני סרטים וסרטונים. ביכולתך להוריד קדימונים ולהוסיף סרטים אל CouchPotato. הרחבה זו מאפשרת גישה לקדימונים מ:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]רובם זמינים באיכויות 480p, 720p ו-1080p</description>
    <description lang="hr">Ovaj dodatak omogućuje pristup filmskim najavama i insertima. Možete preuzeti najave i dodati filmove na CouchPotato. Omogućuje pristup najavama iz:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Većina ih je dostupna u 480p, 720p i 1080p kvaliteti.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a modul hozzáférést biztosít filmajánlókhoz és videóklipekhez a következő weboldalakról:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Legtöbbjük elérhető 480p, 720p és 1080p felbontásban is</description>
    <description lang="it">This Plugin fornisce accesso a Trailer di Film e Filmati dalle seguenti fonti::[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]la maggior parte di questi sono disponibili a 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
    <description lang="ko">이 플러그인은 영화 예고편과 클립을 제공합니다. 예고편을 다운로드할 수 있고 CoachPotato에 영화를 추가할 수 있습니다. 아래 사이트의 예고편에 접속할 수 있습니다:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]대부분의 영상은 480p, 720p, 1080p 포맷을 지원합니다.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Deze Plugin bied toegang tot Film trailers en Clips. U kunt trailers downloaden en films aan CouchPotato toevoegen. Het bied toegang tot Trailers van:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De meeste zijn beschikbaar in 480p, 720p en 1080p kwaliteit.</description>
    <description lang="no">Dette tillegget gir tilgang til filmtrailere og -snutter. Du kan laste ned trailere og legge filmer til CouchPotato. Den gir tilgang til trailere fra:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]]De fleste er tilgjengelig i 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="pl">Ten Plugin daje dostęp do zwiastunów filmowych i klipów z następujących źródeł:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]Większość z nich jest dostępna w 480p, 720p i 1080p</description>
    <description lang="pt">Este plugin permite-lhe ver trailers e clipes de filmes a partir das seguintes fontes:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]A maior parte deles está disponível em 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este plugin fornece acesso a trailers de filmes e clipes das seguintes fontes:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]A maioria deles está disponível em 480p, 720p e 1080p</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento doplnok poskytuje prístup k ukážkam filmov a ku klipom z týchto zdrojov:&amp;#10; - apple.com&amp;#10; - yahoo.com&amp;#10; - youtube.com&amp;#10; - moviefone.com&amp;#10; - ign.com&amp;#10; - hd-trailers.net&amp;#10; - aol.com&amp;#10;Väčšina z nich je dostupná v rozlíšení 480p, 720p a 1080p.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Detta plugin tillhandahåller trailers hämtade från följande källor:[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]De flesta är tillgängliga i 480p, 720p and 1080p</description>
    <description lang="zh">本插件提供访问预告片和电影剪辑。你可以下载预告片和将电影加入到CouchPotato。支持访问以下来源的预告片：[CR]- apple.com[CR]- yahoo.com[CR]- youtube.com[CR]- moviefone.com[CR]- ign.com[CR]- hd-trailers.net[CR]- aol.com[CR]大多为480p、720p和1080p</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.chardet" name="chardet" version="4.0.0" provider-name="Character Encoding Detector">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">The Universal Character Encoding Detector</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Universal Character Encoding Detector</description>
    <license>LGPL-2.1</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>https://chardet.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/chardet/chardet</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
